<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Envelope>
 <Body>
  <add_adverts>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>VmA004</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>155000</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>appartement</habitat>
    <latitude>40.46366700</latitude>
    <longitude>-3.74922000</longitude>
    <mandate_number>VmA004</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[New promotion of 2 and 3 bedroom apartments]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[Nueva promoción de apartamentos de 2 y 3 Dromitorios]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[Nouvelle promotion d&#39;appartements de 2 et 3 chambres]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[Neue Förderung von 2 und 3 Schlafzimmern]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[Nuova promozione di appartamenti da 2 e 3 camere da letto]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[This new development consists of 48 homes distributed in ground floor, 1st and 2nd floor and attics. (On sale the 1st phase of 27 homes).

Homes of 2 and 3 bedrooms, 2 bathrooms, living room, open kitchen equipped with high and low furniture, ceramic hob, electric oven and extractor fan.

Homes with large windows, bright and sunny, large terraces from which to enjoy beautiful views of the countryside and the Montgó. Ideal as holiday homes or as a first home.

The building also has a basement with parking spaces and storage rooms (optional).

As for the common areas, highlight the large garden, swimming pool for adults and another for children, paddle tennis and a recreational area for children.

Start date of works: Immediate
Completion date of the works: end July 2019

The promotion is in the municipality of Denia, on the beach front and very close to the towns of Denia and Oliva. The Shopping Center in Ondara is less than 7 km away. The golf of Oliva is 9 km away. The airports of Alicante and Valencia are 103 and 112 km away respectively]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[Esta nueva promoción consta de 48 viviendas distribuidas en planta baja, 1º y 2º planta y áticos. (A la venta la 1º fase de 27 viviendas). 

Viviendas de 2 y 3 dormitorios, 2 baños, salón comedor, cocina abierta equipada con muebles altos y bajos, vitrocerámica, horno eléctrico y campana extractora. 

Viviendas con grandes ventanales, luminosas y soleadas, grandes terrazas desde donde disfrutar de unas bonitas vistas al campo y al Montgó. Ideales como viviendas de vacaciones o como primera residencia.

El edificio también dispone de una planta sótano con plazas de parking y trasteros (opcional).

En cuanto a las zonas comunes, destacar el amplio jardín, piscina para adultos y otra para niños, pista de pádel y una zona recreativa infantil.

Fecha de inicio de obras: Inmediata
Fecha de finalización de las obras: final julio de 2019

La promoción está en el termino municipal  de Denia, a  primera línea de las playas   y muy cerca de las poblaciones de Denia y Oliva. El Centro Comercial en Ondara está a menos de 7 km. El golf de Oliva está a 9 km. Los aeropuertos de Alicante y Valencia están a 103 y 112 km respectivamente]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[Ce nouveau développement se compose de 48 maisons réparties en rez-de-chaussée, 1er et 2ème étage et greniers. (En vente la 1ère phase de 27 logements).

Logement 2 et 3 chambres, 2 salles de bains, salon, cuisine ouverte avec des unités de base et le mur, plaque de cuisson, four et extracteur.

Maisons avec de grandes fenêtres, lumineux et ensoleillé, grandes terrasses pour profiter de belles vues sur la campagne et le Montgo. Idéal comme maison de vacances ou comme première maison.

Le bâtiment dispose également d&#39;un sous-sol avec des places de parking et des salles de stockage (en option).

En ce qui concerne les parties communes, mettant en lumière le grand jardin, piscine pour adultes et enfants, court de paddle-tennis et aire de jeux.

Date de début des travaux: Immédiat
Date d&#39;achèvement des travaux: fin juillet 2019

La promotion est dans la municipalité de Denia, sur le front de mer et très proche des villes de Denia et Oliva. Le centre commercial d&#39;Ondara est à moins de 7 km. Le golf d&#39;Oliva est à 9 km. Les aéroports d&#39;Alicante et de Valence sont respectivement à 103 et 112 km]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Diese neue Entwicklung besteht aus 48 Häusern im Erdgeschoss, 1. und 2. Stock und Dachböden verteilt. (Im Verkauf die 1. Phase von 27 Häusern).

Häuser von 2 und 3 Schlafzimmern, 2 Badezimmern, Wohnzimmer, offene Küche mit hohen und niedrigen Möbeln, Ceran-Kochfeld, Elektroherd und Dunstabzugshaube.

Häuser mit großen Fenstern, hell und sonnig, große Terrassen, von denen aus man eine herrliche Aussicht auf die Landschaft und den Montgó genießen kann. Ideal als Ferienhaus oder als erstes Zuhause.

Das Gebäude hat auch einen Keller mit Parkplätzen und Lagerräumen (optional).

Wie für die öffentlichen Bereiche, markieren Sie den großen Garten, Schwimmbad für Erwachsene und ein anderes für Kinder, Paddle-Tennis und ein Naherholungsgebiet für Kinder.

Startdatum der Arbeiten: Sofort
Fertigstellungstermin der Arbeiten: Ende Juli 2019

Die Förderung ist in der Gemeinde von Denia, am Strand und ganz in der Nähe der Städte Denia und Oliva. Das Einkaufszentrum in Ondara ist weniger als 7 km entfernt. Der Golfplatz von Oliva liegt 9 km entfernt. Die Flughäfen von Alicante und Valencia sind 103 bzw. 112 km entfernt]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[Questo nuovo sviluppo è costituito da 48 case distribuite al piano terra, 1 ° e 2 ° piano e mansarde. (In vendita la prima fase di 27 case).

Case di 2 e 3 camere da letto, 2 bagni, soggiorno, cucina aperta attrezzata con mobili alti e bassi, piano cottura in vetroceramica, forno elettrico e cappa aspirante.

Case con ampie finestre, luminose e soleggiate, ampie terrazze dalle quali godere di una splendida vista sulla campagna e sul Montgó. Ideale come casa vacanza o come prima casa.

L&#39;edificio ha anche una cantina con posti auto e ripostigli (opzionale).

Per quanto riguarda le aree comuni, evidenzia l&#39;ampio giardino, la piscina per adulti e un&#39;altra per bambini, paddle tennis e un&#39;area ricreativa per bambini.

Data di inizio dei lavori: immediata
Data di completamento dei lavori: fine luglio 2019

La promozione è nel comune di Denia, di fronte alla spiaggia e molto vicino alle città di Denia e Oliva. Il centro commerciale di Ondara dista meno di 7 km. Il campo da golf di Oliva dista 9 km. Gli aeroporti di Alicante e Valencia distano rispettivamente 103 e 112 km]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>95</h_surface>
    <n_beds>2</n_beds>
    <n_baths>2</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>0</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5402/greenacres/5ad776293d489_ii.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5402/greenacres/5ad7762d7d4d2_i.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5402/greenacres/5ad7762fe0beb_iii.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>top-30</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>119000</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>old</habitat>
    <latitude>38.85129750</latitude>
    <longitude>0.01619532</longitude>
    <mandate_number>top-30</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[Fantastic townhouse in the center of Els Poblets]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[Fantástico adosado en el centro de Els Poblets]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[Maison de ville fantastique dans le centre de Els Poblets]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[Fantastisches Stadthaus im Zentrum von Els Poblets]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[Residenza di città fantastica nel centro di Els Poblets]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[The house is distributed on two levels and consists of 1 dining room, kitchen, 2 bedrooms, 1 bathrooms and 1 toilet. Outside we have the terrace, with enough space to enjoy the outdoors, and the community pool. It is located in the urban center and near the beaches. Very close to the towns of Denia and Oliva. The Shopping Center in Ondara is less than 7 km away. The golf of Oliva is 9 km away. The airports of Alicante and Valencia are 103 and 112 km away respectively.]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[La vivienda se distribuye en dos niveles y consta de 1 sala comedor, cocina, 2dormitorios, 1baños y 1 aseo. En el exterior tenemos la terraza, con espacio suficiente para disfrutar del aire libre, y la piscina comunitaria. Se localiza  en el centro urbano y cerca  de las playas. Muy cerca de las poblaciones de Denia y Oliva. El Centro Comercial en Ondara está a menos de 7 km. El golf de Oliva está a 9 km. Los aeropuertos de Alicante y Valencia están a 103 y 112 km respectivamente.]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[La maison est distribuée sur deux niveaux et se compose de 1 salle à manger, cuisine, 2 chambres, 1 salle de bain et 1 toilette. Dehors, nous avons la terrasse, avec suffisamment d&#39;espace pour profiter de l&#39;extérieur, et la piscine communautaire. Il est situé dans le centre urbain et à proximité des plages. Très proche des villes de Denia et Oliva. Le centre commercial d&#39;Ondara est à moins de 7 km. Le golf d&#39;Oliva est à 9 km. Les aéroports d&#39;Alicante et de Valence sont respectivement à 103 et 112 km.]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Das Haus ist auf zwei Ebenen verteilt und besteht aus 1 Esszimmer, Küche, 2 Schlafzimmer, 1 Badezimmer und 1 Toilette. Draußen haben wir die Terrasse, mit genug Platz, um die Natur zu genießen, und den Gemeinschaftspool. Es befindet sich im Stadtzentrum und in der Nähe der Strände. Ganz in der Nähe der Städte Denia und Oliva. Das Einkaufszentrum in Ondara ist weniger als 7 km entfernt. Der Golfplatz von Oliva liegt 9 km entfernt. Die Flughäfen von Alicante und Valencia sind 103 bzw. 112 km entfernt.]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[La casa è distribuita su due livelli ed è composta da 1 sala da pranzo, cucina, 2 camere da letto, 1 bagno e 1 WC. All&#39;esterno abbiamo la terrazza, con spazio sufficiente per godersi la vita all&#39;aria aperta, e la piscina della comunità. Si trova nel centro urbano e vicino alle spiagge. Molto vicino alle città di Denia e Oliva. Il centro commerciale di Ondara dista meno di 7 km. Il campo da golf di Oliva dista 9 km. Gli aeroporti di Alicante e Valencia distano rispettivamente 103 e 112 km.]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>73</h_surface>
    <n_beds>2</n_beds>
    <n_baths>2</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>0</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5431/greenacres/image00010.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5431/greenacres/image00001.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5431/greenacres/image00002.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5431/greenacres/image00004.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5431/greenacres/image00003.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5431/greenacres/image00006.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5431/greenacres/image00005.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5431/greenacres/image00007.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5431/greenacres/image00008.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5431/greenacres/image00009.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>VmH005</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>279000</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>luxury</habitat>
    <latitude>38.86321010</latitude>
    <longitude>0.01595900</longitude>
    <mandate_number>VmH005</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[Nueva construcción]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[Nueva construcción]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[Nueva construcción]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[Nueva construcción]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[Nueva construcción]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[NUEVA PROMOCION: Villas independientes con parcela privada. Diseño moderno y funcional. 3 dormitorios dobles, 2 baños (1 en suite), salón comedor, cocina americana, lavadero, terraza cubierta y gran terraza solarium de hasta 122 m2.
124 m2 construidos. Piscina privada incluida.
Primera calidad. Consúltenos sin compromiso]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[NUEVA PROMOCION: Villas independientes con parcela privada. Diseño moderno y funcional. 3 dormitorios dobles, 2 baños (1 en suite), salón comedor, cocina americana, lavadero, terraza cubierta y gran terraza solarium de hasta 122 m2.
124 m2 construidos. Piscina privada incluida.
Primera calidad. Consúltenos sin compromiso]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[NUEVA PROMOCION: Villas independientes con parcela privada. Diseño moderno y funcional. 3 dormitorios dobles, 2 baños (1 en suite), salón comedor, cocina americana, lavadero, terraza cubierta y gran terraza solarium de hasta 122 m2.
124 m2 construidos. Piscina privada incluida.
Primera calidad. Consúltenos sin compromiso]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[NUEVA PROMOCION: Villas independientes con parcela privada. Diseño moderno y funcional. 3 dormitorios dobles, 2 baños (1 en suite), salón comedor, cocina americana, lavadero, terraza cubierta y gran terraza solarium de hasta 122 m2.
124 m2 construidos. Piscina privada incluida.
Primera calidad. Consúltenos sin compromiso]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[NUEVA PROMOCION: Villas independientes con parcela privada. Diseño moderno y funcional. 3 dormitorios dobles, 2 baños (1 en suite), salón comedor, cocina americana, lavadero, terraza cubierta y gran terraza solarium de hasta 122 m2.
124 m2 construidos. Piscina privada incluida.
Primera calidad. Consúltenos sin compromiso]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>123</h_surface>
    <l_surface>360</l_surface>
    <n_beds>3</n_beds>
    <n_baths>2</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>0</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5480/greenacres/infografia.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5480/greenacres/5af2dcfc79cfd_sinttulo.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5480/greenacres/5af2dd007fe62_sinttulo2.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5480/greenacres/5af2dd016f85c_sinttulo1.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5480/greenacres/5af2dd0280c8a_sinttulo4.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>A357</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>129990</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>appartement</habitat>
    <latitude>38.86431730</latitude>
    <longitude>-0.00559570</longitude>
    <mandate_number>A357</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[Apartment in Vergel]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[Apartamento en Vergel]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[Appartement à Vergel]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[Ferienwohnung in Vergel]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[Appartamento a Vergel]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[Apartment on ground floor very close to the beach (about 600 m) and all services. With large terrace as well as community pool. Apartment with 2 double bedrooms, 2 bathrooms, large living room, fully equipped kitchen. Parking and Storage. Contact us without obligation.]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[Apartamento en planta baja muy  cercano a la playa (unos 600 m) y de todos los servicios. Con amplia terraza  así como también piscina comunitaria. Apartamento de 2 dormitorios dobles, 2 baños, amplio salón comedor, cocina totalmente equipada. Parking y Trastero . Consúltenos sin compromiso.]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[Appartement au rez-de-chaussée très proche de la plage (environ 600 m) et de tous les services. Avec une grande terrasse ainsi qu&#39;une piscine communautaire. Appartement avec 2 chambres doubles, 2 salles de bains, grand salon, cuisine entièrement équipée. Parking et entreposage. Contactez-nous sans engagement.]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Wohnung im Erdgeschoss sehr nahe am Strand (ca. 600 m) und alle Dienstleistungen. Mit großer Terrasse sowie Gemeinschaftspool. Wohnung mit 2 Schlafzimmern, 2 Bäder, großes Wohnzimmer, voll ausgestattete Küche. Parkplatz und Lagerung. Kontaktieren Sie uns unverbindlich.]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[Appartamento al piano terra molto vicino alla spiaggia (circa 600 m) e tutti i servizi. Con ampia terrazza e piscina comunitaria. Appartamento con 2 camere da letto matrimoniali, 2 bagni, ampio soggiorno, cucina completamente attrezzata. Parcheggio e deposito. Contattaci senza obbligo.]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>70</h_surface>
    <n_beds>2</n_beds>
    <n_baths>2</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>1</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4446/greenacres/p7200038.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4446/greenacres/p7200039.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4446/greenacres/p7200040.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4446/greenacres/p7200041.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4446/greenacres/p7200042.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4446/greenacres/p7200043.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4446/greenacres/p7200045.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4446/greenacres/p7200044.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4446/greenacres/p7200046.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4446/greenacres/p7200048.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4446/greenacres/p7200049.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4446/greenacres/p7200051.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4446/greenacres/p7200053.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="14"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4446/greenacres/p7200050.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="15"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4446/greenacres/p7200055.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="16"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4446/greenacres/p7200054.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="17"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4446/greenacres/p7200057.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="18"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4446/greenacres/p7200059.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="19"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4446/greenacres/p7200058.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="20"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4446/greenacres/p7200062.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="21"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4446/greenacres/p7200063.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="22"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4446/greenacres/p7200064.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="23"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4446/greenacres/p7200065.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="24"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4446/greenacres/p7200067.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="25"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4446/greenacres/p7200069.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="26"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4446/greenacres/p7200068.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>B397b</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>160000</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>old</habitat>
    <latitude>38.86508210</latitude>
    <longitude>-0.00792010</longitude>
    <mandate_number>B397b</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[ADOSADO]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[ADOSADO]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[ADOSADO]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[ADOSADO]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[ADOSADO]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[Gran adosado seminuevo. Cercano a la playa (750 m) así como de todos los servicios. Amplia terraza y jardín .Adosados compuesto por  3 dormitorios, 2 baños ,salón comedor, cocina independiente. Primeras calidades (Ventanas de PVC, climalit, persianas...)Muebles y electrodomésticos incluidos. Piscina comunitaria.Consúltenos sin compromiso]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[Gran adosado seminuevo. Cercano a la playa (750 m) así como de todos los servicios. Amplia terraza y jardín .Adosados compuesto por  3 dormitorios, 2 baños ,salón comedor, cocina independiente. Primeras calidades (Ventanas de PVC, climalit, persianas...)Muebles y electrodomésticos incluidos. Piscina comunitaria.Consúltenos sin compromiso]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[Gran adosado seminuevo. Cercano a la playa (750 m) así como de todos los servicios. Amplia terraza y jardín .Adosados compuesto por  3 dormitorios, 2 baños ,salón comedor, cocina independiente. Primeras calidades (Ventanas de PVC, climalit, persianas...)Muebles y electrodomésticos incluidos. Piscina comunitaria.Consúltenos sin compromiso]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Gran adosado seminuevo. Cercano a la playa (750 m) así como de todos los servicios. Amplia terraza y jardín .Adosados compuesto por  3 dormitorios, 2 baños ,salón comedor, cocina independiente. Primeras calidades (Ventanas de PVC, climalit, persianas...)Muebles y electrodomésticos incluidos. Piscina comunitaria.Consúltenos sin compromiso]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[Gran adosado seminuevo. Cercano a la playa (750 m) así como de todos los servicios. Amplia terraza y jardín .Adosados compuesto por  3 dormitorios, 2 baños ,salón comedor, cocina independiente. Primeras calidades (Ventanas de PVC, climalit, persianas...)Muebles y electrodomésticos incluidos. Piscina comunitaria.Consúltenos sin compromiso]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>156</h_surface>
    <n_beds>3</n_beds>
    <n_baths>2</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>0</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3816/greenacres/pa140001.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3816/greenacres/pa140002.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3816/greenacres/pa140003.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3816/greenacres/pa140005.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3816/greenacres/pa140004.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3816/greenacres/pa140008.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3816/greenacres/pa140009.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3816/greenacres/pa140010.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3816/greenacres/pa140012.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3816/greenacres/pa140011.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3816/greenacres/pa140014.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3816/greenacres/pa140015.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3816/greenacres/pa140016.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="14"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3816/greenacres/pa140017.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="15"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3816/greenacres/pa140018.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="16"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3816/greenacres/pa140020.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="17"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3816/greenacres/pa140021.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="18"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3816/greenacres/pa140019.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="19"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3816/greenacres/pa140023.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="20"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3816/greenacres/pa140022.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="21"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3816/greenacres/pa140026.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="22"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3816/greenacres/pa140024.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="23"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3816/greenacres/pa140029.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="24"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3816/greenacres/pa140028.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="25"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3816/greenacres/pa140030.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="26"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3816/greenacres/pa140031.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>A332</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>98000</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>appartement</habitat>
    <latitude>38.86914476</latitude>
    <longitude>-0.01150237</longitude>
    <mandate_number>A332</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[Apartment]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[Apartamento]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[Appartement]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[Wohnung]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[Appartamento]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[OPPORTUNITY. Apartment completely refurbished with views spectacular to the sea very close to the beach (some 100 m) as well as of all them services. With 2 large terraces, garden and communal pool, tennis. Apartment with 3 bedrooms, 2 bathrooms, dining room, furniture, appliances. Contact us without obligation.]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[OPORTUNIDAD.Apartamento completamente reformado con vistas espectaculares al mar muy cercano a la playa (unos 100 m) así como de todos los servicios. Con  2 amplias terrazas, jardín  y piscina  comunitaria, zona de tenis. Apartamento de 3 dormitorios , 2 baños, salón comedor, muebles, electrodomésticos . Consúltenos sin compromiso.]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[OPORTUNIDAD.Apartamento completamente reformado con vistas espectaculares al mar muy cercano a la playa (unos 100 m) así como de todos los servicios. Con  2 amplias terrazas, jardín  y piscina  comunitaria, zona de tenis. Apartamento de 3 dormitorios , 2 baños, salón comedor, muebles, electrodomésticos . Consúltenos sin compromiso.]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[GELEGENHEIT. Komplett renoviertes Apartment mit spektakulärem Ausblick auf das Meer in unmittelbarer Nähe zum Strand (100 m) sowie alle Dienstleistungen. Mit 2 großen Terrassen, Garten und Pool Gemeinschaft, Bereich Tennis. Apartment mit 3 Schlafzimmern, 2 Bäder, Esszimmer, Möbel, Haushaltsgeräte. Kontaktieren Sie uns unverbindlich.]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[OPORTUNIDAD.Apartamento completamente reformado con vistas espectaculares al mar muy cercano a la playa (unos 100 m) así como de todos los servicios. Con  2 amplias terrazas, jardín  y piscina  comunitaria, zona de tenis. Apartamento de 3 dormitorios , 2 baños, salón comedor, muebles, electrodomésticos . Consúltenos sin compromiso.]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>96</h_surface>
    <n_beds>3</n_beds>
    <n_baths>2</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>1</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1625/greenacres/dsc1100.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1625/greenacres/2015080514.10.18.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1625/greenacres/dsc1093.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1625/greenacres/dsc1102.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1625/greenacres/dsc1104.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1625/greenacres/dsc1108.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1625/greenacres/dsc1106.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1625/greenacres/dsc1109.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1625/greenacres/dsc1113.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1625/greenacres/dsc1116.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1625/greenacres/dsc1117.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1625/greenacres/dsc1124.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1625/greenacres/dsc1130.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="14"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1625/greenacres/dsc1138.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="15"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1625/greenacres/dsc1148.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="16"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1625/greenacres/dsc1155.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="17"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1625/greenacres/dsc2779.jpg.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="18"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1625/greenacres/dsc2844.jpg.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="19"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1625/greenacres/dsc2853.jpg.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="20"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1625/greenacres/dsc2861.jpg.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="21"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1625/greenacres/dsc2883.jpg.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="22"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1625/greenacres/dsc2879.jpg.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="23"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1625/greenacres/dsc2905.jpg.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="24"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1625/greenacres/dsc2910.jpg.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="25"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1625/greenacres/2015080514.11.03.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>H553</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>195000</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>luxury</habitat>
    <latitude>38.86313090</latitude>
    <longitude>0.01630880</longitude>
    <mandate_number>H553</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[COTTAGE]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[CHALET]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[CHALET]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[FERIENHAUS]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[COTTAGE]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[Villa in a private plot of 418m 2 in the town of Els Poblets, 800 m from the beach, close to Denia and Oliva, as well as all the services. Location very quiet, very clear and beautiful views. Excellent state of conservation. It consists of two bedrooms and a bathroom, kitchen Office. Fully renovated, furnished with appliances included. Garage on surface. Sunroom. Cold air heat pump heating, mosquito nets in windows, bars on windows. Contact us without obligation.]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[Chalet en parcela privada de 418m2 en la tranquila población de Els Poblets, a 800 m de la playa, muy cerca de Denia y de Oliva, así como también de todos los servicios. Emplazamiento muy tranquilo, vistas muy despejadas y bonitas. Excelente estado de conservación. Consta de dos dormitorios y un baño, cocina en office. Completamente reformado, amueblado con electrodomésticos incluidos. Garaje en superficie. Terraza acristalada. Calefacción por bomba de aire frío calor, mosquiteras en ventanas, rejas en ventanas. Consúltenos sin compromiso.]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[Villa dans une parcelle privée de 418m 2 dans la ville d’Els Poblets, à 800 m de la plage, près de Denia et Oliva, ainsi que tous les services. Vues de très calmes, très clairs et belles emplacement. Excellent état de conservation. Il se compose de deux chambres et une salle de bains, cuisine, bureau. Entièrement rénové, meublé avec appareils inclus. Garage sur la surface. Verrière. Pompe à chaleur air froid chauffage, moustiquaires dans les fenêtres, barres sur windows. Contactez-nous sans obligation.]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Villa auf einem privaten Grundstück von 418m 2 in der Stadt von Els Poblets, 800 m vom Strand entfernt, in der Nähe von Denia und Oliva, sowie alle Dienstleistungen. Lage sehr ruhig, sehr klare und schöne Aussicht. Ausgezeichneten Zustand der Erhaltung. Es besteht aus zwei Schlafzimmer und ein Badezimmer, Küche, Büro. Komplett renoviert, ausgestattet mit Geräten enthalten. Garage auf Oberfläche. Wintergarten. Kalte Luftwärmepumpe Heizung, Moskitonetzen in Windows, Bars auf Windows. Kontaktieren Sie uns unverbindlich.]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[Villa in un terreno privato di 418m 2 nella città di Els Poblets, 800 m dalla spiaggia, vicino a Denia e Oliva, nonché tutti i servizi. Posizione molto tranquilla, molto chiara e bella vista. Ottimo stato di conservazione. Si compone di due camere da letto e un bagno, cucina Office. Completamente ristrutturato, arredato con elettrodomestici inclusi. Garage su superficie. Sunroom. Pompa di calore aria fredda riscaldamento, zanzariere nelle finestre, barre su windows. Contattaci senza impegno.]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>418</h_surface>
    <n_beds>2</n_beds>
    <n_baths>1</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>1</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3583/greenacres/58d8d62f97382_p3250036.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3583/greenacres/58d8d63f43ec3_p3250039.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3583/greenacres/58d8d644487c9_p3250042.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3583/greenacres/58d8d6494a176_p3250043.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3583/greenacres/58d8d64e7ad12_p3250044.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3583/greenacres/58d8d650c679e_p3250040.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3583/greenacres/58d8d6575ca6c_p3250045.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3583/greenacres/58d8d65759d4b_p3250046.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3583/greenacres/58d8d65ee4451_p3250048.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3583/greenacres/58d8d66826218_p3250052.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3583/greenacres/58d8d66c3aea9_p3250057.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3583/greenacres/58d8d66d72793_p3250055.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3583/greenacres/58d8d67500466_p3250060.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="14"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3583/greenacres/58d8d6785b7e9_p3250058.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="15"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3583/greenacres/58d8d67c1a0f2_p3250061.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="16"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3583/greenacres/58d8d6825d775_p3250062.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="17"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3583/greenacres/58d8d68b16949_p3250065.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="18"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3583/greenacres/58d8d68b899e3_p3250063.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="19"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3583/greenacres/58d8d690c66f9_p3250066.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>B409</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>155000</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>old</habitat>
    <latitude>38.85478800</latitude>
    <longitude>0.01727410</longitude>
    <mandate_number>B409</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[Townhouse Corner in Almadraba beach]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[Adosado Esquinero en playa Almadraba]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[Coin de maison de ville dans la plage d&#39;Almadraba]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[Stadthaus Corner in Almadraba Strand]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[Townhouse Corner nella spiaggia di Almadraba]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[The house is divided into two levels and consists of 1 dining room with fireplace, kitchen, 2 double bedrooms and 1 bathroom and a parking for one vehicle for 1 vehicle. Outside we have the naya, with enough space to enjoy the outdoors, and the community pool. The community garden is simple, which implies easy maintenance.
It is located very close to the urban center and the beaches. The house is in the municipality of Els Poblets, 150 meters from the beaches of Almadrava and very close to the towns of Denia and Oliva. The Shopping Center in Ondara is less than 7 km away. The golf of Oliva is 9 km away. The airports of Alicante and Valencia are 103 and 112 km away respectively.]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[La vivienda se destribuye en dos niveles y consta de  1 sala comedor con chimenea, cocina americana, 2 dormitorios dobles y  1 baño y un aparcamiento para un vehículo para 1 vehículo. En el exterior tenemos la naya, con espacio suficiente para disfrutar del aire libre, y la piscina counitaria. El jardín comunitario  es simple, lo que implica una fácil manutención. 
Se localiza muy cerca del centro urbano y de las playas. La casa está en el termino municipal de Els Poblets, a 150 metros  de las playas de Almadrava y muy cerca de las poblaciones de Denia y Oliva. El Centro Comercial en Ondara está a menos de 7 km. El golf de Oliva está a 9 km. Los aeropuertos de Alicante y Valencia están a 103 y 112 km respectivamente.]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[La maison est divisée en deux niveaux et se compose de 1 salle à manger avec cheminée, cuisine, 2 chambres doubles et 1 salle de bain et un parking pour un véhicule pour 1 véhicule. Dehors, nous avons la naya, avec suffisamment d&#39;espace pour profiter de l&#39;extérieur, et la piscine communautaire. Le jardin communautaire est simple, ce qui implique un entretien facile.
Il est situé très près du centre urbain et des plages. La maison est dans la municipalité d&#39;Els Poblets, à 150 mètres des plages d&#39;Almadrava et très proche des villes de Denia et Oliva. Le centre commercial d&#39;Ondara est à moins de 7 km. Le golf d&#39;Oliva est à 9 km. Les aéroports d&#39;Alicante et de Valence sont respectivement à 103 et 112 km.]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Das Haus ist in zwei Ebenen aufgeteilt und besteht aus 1 Esszimmer mit Kamin, Küche, 2 Doppelschlafzimmern und 1 Badezimmer und einem Parkplatz für ein Fahrzeug für 1 Fahrzeug. Draußen haben wir die Naya, mit genug Platz, um die Natur und den Gemeinschaftspool zu genießen. Der Gemeinschaftsgarten ist einfach, was eine einfache Wartung bedeutet.
Es befindet sich in unmittelbarer Nähe des Stadtzentrums und der Strände. Das Haus liegt in der Gemeinde von Els Poblets, 150 Meter von den Stränden von Almadrava und ganz in der Nähe der Städte Denia und Oliva. Das Einkaufszentrum in Ondara ist weniger als 7 km entfernt. Der Golfplatz von Oliva liegt 9 km entfernt. Die Flughäfen von Alicante und Valencia sind 103 bzw. 112 km entfernt.]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[La casa è divisa in due livelli ed è composta da 1 sala da pranzo con camino, cucina, 2 camere matrimoniali e 1 bagno e un parcheggio per un veicolo per 1 veicolo. All&#39;esterno abbiamo il naya, con spazio sufficiente per godersi l&#39;aria aperta e la piscina della comunità. L&#39;orto comunitario è semplice, il che implica una facile manutenzione.
Si trova molto vicino al centro urbano e alle spiagge. La casa si trova nel comune di Els Poblets, a 150 metri dalle spiagge di Almadrava e molto vicino alle città di Denia e Oliva. Il centro commerciale di Ondara dista meno di 7 km. Il campo da golf di Oliva dista 9 km. Gli aeroporti di Alicante e Valencia distano rispettivamente 103 e 112 km.]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>87</h_surface>
    <n_beds>2</n_beds>
    <n_baths>1</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>0</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5381/greenacres/fotos270917052.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5381/greenacres/fotos004.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5381/greenacres/fotos270917010.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5381/greenacres/fotos270917017.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5381/greenacres/fotos270917016.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5381/greenacres/fotos270917019.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5381/greenacres/fotos270917025.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5381/greenacres/fotos270917031.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5381/greenacres/fotos270917034.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5381/greenacres/fotos270917037.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5381/greenacres/fotos270917049.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5381/greenacres/fotos270917054.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5381/greenacres/fotos270917062.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="14"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5381/greenacres/fotos270917058.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="15"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5381/greenacres/fotos270917076.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>H560</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>269000</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>luxury</habitat>
    <latitude>38.83879920</latitude>
    <longitude>0.10505570</longitude>
    <mandate_number>H560</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[Villa with 1000m2 plot]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[Chalet con 1000m2 de parcela]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[Villa avec terrain de 1000m2]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[Villa mit 1000m2 Grundstück]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[Villa con trama 1000m2]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[The property is located on a plot of generous dimensions as it has 1000m2. The house is distributed on one level and consists of 1 dining room with fireplace, kitchen, 4 bedrooms, 2 bathrooms, laundry area and a garage for 1 vehicle. Outside we have the naya, with enough space to enjoy the outdoors, and the kidney-shaped pool of approximately 6 * 4m. The garden is simple, which implies easy maintenance. By means of external stairs we can go up to a terrace with very good panoramic views. The property has air conditioning, outdoor parking space, terrace on the roof, double glazed PVC windows with mosquito nets and bars.
It is located very close to the urban center and the beaches. The house is in the urban area of ​​Els Poblets, 1 km from the beaches of Almadrava and very close to the towns of Denia and Oliva. The Shopping Center in Ondara is less than 7 km away. The golf of Oliva is 9 km away. The airports of Alicante and Valencia are 103 and 112 km away respectively.]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[La propiedad está situada en una parcela de generosas dimensiones ya que dispone de 1000m2. La vivienda se destribuye en un solo nivel y consta de  1 sala comedor con chimenea, cocina, 4 dormitorios, 2 baños, área para lavandería y un garaje para 1 vehículo. En el exterior tenemos la naya, con espacio suficiente para disfrutar del aire libre, y la piscina en forma de riñón de aproximadamente 6*4m. El jardín es simple, lo que implica una fácil manutención. Mediante unas escaleras exteriores podemos subir a una terraza con muy buenas vistas panorámicas. La propiedad posee aire acondicionado, plaza de aparcamiento exterior, terraza sobre el techo, ventanas de PVC de doble cristal con mosquiteras y rejas.
Se localiza muy cerca del centro urbano y de las playas. La casa está en el casco urbano de Els Poblets, a 1 km de las playas de Almadrava y muy cerca de las poblaciones de Denia y Oliva. El Centro Comercial en Ondara está a menos de 7 km. El golf de Oliva está a 9 km. Los aeropuertos de Alicante y Valencia están a 103 y 112 km respectivamente.]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[La propriété est située sur un terrain de dimensions généreuses car elle a 1000m2. La maison est distribuée sur un seul niveau et se compose de 1 salle à manger avec cheminée, cuisine, 4 chambres, 2 salles de bains, buanderie et un garage pour 1 véhicule. Dehors, nous avons la naya, avec suffisamment d&#39;espace pour profiter de l&#39;extérieur, et la piscine en forme de rein d&#39;environ 6 * 4m. Le jardin est simple, ce qui implique un entretien facile. Au moyen d&#39;escaliers extérieurs, nous pouvons monter à une terrasse avec de très bonnes vues panoramiques. La propriété dispose de la climatisation, parking extérieur, terrasse sur le toit, double vitrage PVC avec moustiquaires et des bars.
Il est situé très près du centre urbain et des plages. La maison est dans la zone urbaine d&#39;Els Poblets, à 1 km des plages d&#39;Almadrava et très proche des villes de Denia et Oliva. Le centre commercial d&#39;Ondara est à moins de 7 km. Le golf d&#39;Oliva est à 9 km. Les aéroports d&#39;Alicante et de Valence sont respectivement à 103 et 112 km.]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Das Anwesen befindet sich auf einem Grundstück von großzügigen Abmessungen, da es 1000m2 hat. Das Haus ist auf einer Ebene verteilt und besteht aus 1 Esszimmer mit Kamin, Küche, 4 Schlafzimmern, 2 Bädern, Waschküche und einer Garage für 1 Fahrzeug. Draußen haben wir die Naya, mit genug Platz, um die Natur zu genießen, und den nierenförmigen Pool von ca. 6 * 4m. Der Garten ist einfach, was eine einfache Wartung bedeutet. Über eine Außentreppe können wir auf eine Terrasse mit sehr guten Panoramablicken gehen. Das Anwesen verfügt über Klimaanlage, Parkplatz im Freien, Terrasse auf dem Dach, doppelt verglaste PVC-Fenster mit Moskitonetzen und Bars.
Es befindet sich in unmittelbarer Nähe des Stadtzentrums und der Strände. Das Haus liegt im Stadtgebiet von Els Poblets, 1 km von den Stränden von Almadrava und ganz in der Nähe der Städte Denia und Oliva. Das Einkaufszentrum in Ondara ist weniger als 7 km entfernt. Der Golfplatz von Oliva liegt 9 km entfernt. Die Flughäfen von Alicante und Valencia sind 103 bzw. 112 km entfernt.]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[La proprietà si trova su un terreno di dimensioni generose in quanto ha 1000m2. La casa è distribuita su un unico livello ed è composta da 1 sala da pranzo con camino, cucina, 4 camere da letto, 2 bagni, zona lavanderia e un garage per 1 veicolo. All&#39;esterno abbiamo il naya, con spazio sufficiente per godersi la vita all&#39;aria aperta, e la piscina a forma di rene di circa 6 * 4 m. Il giardino è semplice, il che implica una facile manutenzione. Per mezzo di scale esterne possiamo salire su una terrazza con viste panoramiche molto buone. La proprietà è dotata di aria condizionata, posto auto esterno, terrazza sul tetto, finestre con doppi vetri in PVC con zanzariere e bar.
Si trova molto vicino al centro urbano e alle spiagge. La casa si trova nella zona urbana di Els Poblets, a 1 km dalle spiagge di Almadrava e molto vicino alle città di Denia e Oliva. Il centro commerciale di Ondara dista meno di 7 km. Il campo da golf di Oliva dista 9 km. Gli aeroporti di Alicante e Valencia distano rispettivamente 103 e 112 km.]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>1000</h_surface>
    <n_beds>4</n_beds>
    <n_baths>3</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>0</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5380/greenacres/p3090110.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5380/greenacres/p3090108.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5380/greenacres/p3090107.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5380/greenacres/p3090109.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5380/greenacres/p3090113.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5380/greenacres/p3090114.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5380/greenacres/p3090115.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5380/greenacres/p3090116.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5380/greenacres/p3090117.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5380/greenacres/p3090118.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5380/greenacres/p3090119.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5380/greenacres/p3090122.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5380/greenacres/p3090120.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="14"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5380/greenacres/p3090127.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="15"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5380/greenacres/p3090123.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="16"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5380/greenacres/p3090128.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="17"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5380/greenacres/p3090129.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="18"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5380/greenacres/p3090134.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="19"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5380/greenacres/p3090135.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="20"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/5380/greenacres/p3090131.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>B369</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>125000</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>old</habitat>
    <latitude>38.85802965</latitude>
    <longitude>0.03070660</longitude>
    <mandate_number>B369</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[TERRACED HOUSE]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[ADOSADO]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[MAISON MITOYENNE]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[REIHENHAUS]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[CASA A SCHIERA]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[TERRACED HOUSE. Very good opportunity, townhouse duplex close to the beach and all services. Spacious terrace cy private garden and swimming pool, as well as community garden. Apartment with 2 bedrooms, 2 bathrooms, 1 toilet, living room, kitchen, first quality (windows and blinds aluminum, double-glazed,... blast door) ... Semifurnished. Contact us without obligation.]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[ADOSADO. Muy buena oportunidad, adosado dúplex cercano a la playa y de todos los servicios. Amplias terraza  cy jardin privado y piscina comunitaria, así como también jardín comunitario .Apartamento de 2 dormitorios, 2 baños, 1 aseo, salón comedor, cocina office, Primeras calidades(ventanas y persianas aluminio, doble acristalamiento, puerta blindada...)... Semiamueblado. Consúltenos sin compromiso.]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[MAISON MITOYENNE. Très belle opportunité, maison de ville duplex proche de la plage et de tous les services. Terrasse spacieuse cy jardin privé et communautaire de la piscine, ainsi qu’aussi jardin communautaire. Appartement avec 2 chambres à coucher, 2 salles de bains, 1 toilette, salon, cuisine, de première qualité (fenêtres et Stores aluminium, double vitrage,... porte de blast) ... Semifurnished. Contactez-nous sans obligation.]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[REIHENHAUS. Sehr gute Gelegenheit, Reihenhaus duplex Nähe Strand und dieser Dienste. Geräumige Terrasse cy privaten Garten und Schwimmbad, sowie Gemeinschaftsgarten. Apartment mit 2 Schlafzimmer, 2 Bäder, 1 WC, Wohnzimmer, Küche, erstklassige (Fenster und Jalousien aus Aluminium, doppelt verglast,... Brandschutztür) ... Semifurnished. Kontaktieren Sie uns unverbindlich.]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[CASA A SCHIERA. Molto buona occasione, casa a schiera duplex vicino alla spiaggia e tutti i servizi. Giardino privato di cy di spaziosa terrazza e la piscina, nonché giardino comunitario. Appartamento con 2 camere da letto, 2 bagni, 1 WC, soggiorno, cucina, prima qualità (finestre e persiane in alluminio, doppi vetro,... porta blindata) ... SEMIARREDATO. Contattaci senza impegno.]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>70</h_surface>
    <n_beds>2</n_beds>
    <n_baths>2</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>1</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1627/greenacres/campolivar.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1627/greenacres/bao.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1627/greenacres/dormit1.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1627/greenacres/dormit2.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1627/greenacres/cocina.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1627/greenacres/p8080288.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1627/greenacres/jardin.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1627/greenacres/p8080289.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1627/greenacres/p8080290.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1627/greenacres/p8080293.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1627/greenacres/p8080292.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1627/greenacres/saloncomdr.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1627/greenacres/salonocomedor.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="14"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1627/greenacres/terraza.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>A327</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>156900</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>appartement</habitat>
    <latitude>38.86509807</latitude>
    <longitude>-0.00607272</longitude>
    <mandate_number>A327</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[Apartment]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[Apartamento]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[Appartement]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[Wohnung]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[Appartamento]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[Apartment close to the playa(600 m) and of all those services (1000 m). With spacious terrace and pool community, as well as also garden community. Apartment of 2 bedrooms, 2 bathrooms, lounge dining room, kitchen independent, wide terrace with view to the garden community. First calidades(ventanas aluminio, doble acristalamiento, persianas aluminio, puerta seguridad...)... Garage with storage room. Fully equipped. Contact us without obligation.]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[Apartamento cercano a la playa(600 m) y de todos los servicios (1000 m). Con amplias terraza y piscina comunitaria, así como también jardín comunitario .Apartamento de 2 dormitorios, 2 baños, salón comedor , cocina independiente, amplia terraza con vista al jardin comunitario. Primeras calidades(ventanas aluminio, doble acristalamiento, persianas aluminio, puerta seguridad...).. Garaje con trastero. Completamente equipado. Consúltenos sin compromiso.]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[Apartamento cercano a la playa(600 m) y de todos los servicios (1000 m). Con amplias terraza y piscina comunitaria, así como también jardín comunitario .Apartamento de 2 dormitorios, 2 baños, salón comedor , cocina independiente, amplia terraza con vista al jardin comunitario. Primeras calidades(ventanas aluminio, doble acristalamiento, persianas aluminio, puerta seguridad...).. Garaje con trastero. Completamente equipado. Consúltenos sin compromiso.]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Appartement in der Nähe der playa(600 m) und der all jene Dienstleistungen (1000 m). Mit Terrasse und Schwimmbad, sowie auch Gemeinschaftsgarten. Wohnung mit 2 Schlafzimmer, 2 Bäder, Wohnzimmer, Küche, Terrasse mit Blick auf den Garten. Ersten Calidades (Ventanas Aluminio, Doble Acristalamiento, Persianas Aluminio Puerta Seguridad...)... Garage mit Abstellraum. Komplett ausgestattet. Kontaktieren Sie uns unverbindlich.]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[Appartamento vicino al playa(600 m) e servizi alberghieri (1000 m). Con spaziosa terrazza e piscina, così come anche giardino comunitario. Appartamento di 2 camere da letto, 2 bagni, soggiorno, cucina, terrazza con vista sul giardino. Prima qualità (alluminio finestre, doppi vetri, persiane in alluminio, sicurezza porta...)... Garage con ripostiglio. Completamente attrezzata. Consultateci senza impegno.]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>91</h_surface>
    <n_beds>2</n_beds>
    <n_baths>2</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>1</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1624/greenacres/p5270074.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1624/greenacres/p5270054.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1624/greenacres/p5270055.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1624/greenacres/p5270058.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1624/greenacres/p5270057.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1624/greenacres/p5270059.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1624/greenacres/p5270060.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1624/greenacres/p5270063.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1624/greenacres/p5270061.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1624/greenacres/p5270064.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1624/greenacres/p5270068.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1624/greenacres/p5270070.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1624/greenacres/p5270069.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="14"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1624/greenacres/p5270071.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="15"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1624/greenacres/p5270073.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="16"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1624/greenacres/p5270077.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="17"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1624/greenacres/p5270079.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>H551</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>255000</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>luxury</habitat>
    <latitude>38.85592000</latitude>
    <longitude>0.01478000</longitude>
    <mandate_number>H551</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[COTTAGE]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[CHALET]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[CHALET]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[FERIENHAUS]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[COTTAGE]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[Independent villa with plot of 400 m2, very quiet. 3dormitorios double, 2 bathrooms (1 en-suite), living room with fireplace cassete, living room with fireplace cassette, kitchen American, laundry, covered terrace, solarium and private pool... Furniture and household appliances. Contact us without obligation]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[Chalet independiente con parcela de 400 m2, en una fantastica zona muy tranquila. 3dormitorios dobles, 2 baños (1 en suite), salón comedor con chimenea cassete, salón comedor con chimenea casete, cocina americana, lavadero, terraza cubierta, solarium, piscina privada... Muebles y electrodomésticos. Consúltenos sin compromiso]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[Maison indépendante avec terrain de 400 m2, très calme. 3dormitorios double, 2 salles de bain (1 en-suite), salle de séjour avec cheminée CD, salon avec cassette de cheminée, cuisine américaine, buanderie, couvraient terrasse, solarium et piscine privée... Appareils de meubles et de ménage. Contactez-nous sans engagement]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Freistehende Villa mit Grundstück von 400 m2, sehr ruhig. 3dormitorios Doppel, bedeckt 2 Bäder (1 En-Suite), Wohnzimmer mit Kamin Cassete, Wohnzimmer mit Kaminkassette, amerikanische Küche, Wäscherei, privater Pool, Terrasse und Solarium... Möbel und Haushaltsgeräte. Kontaktieren Sie uns unverbindlich]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[Villa indipendente con terreno di 400 m2, molto tranquillo. 3dormitorios doppie, 2 bagni (1 bagno), salotto con camino cassete, soggiorno con camino, cucina americana, servizio di lavanderia, coperto terrazza, solarium e piscina privata... Mobili ed elettrodomestici. Contattaci senza impegno]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>400</h_surface>
    <n_beds>3</n_beds>
    <n_baths>2</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>1</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3432/greenacres/fachada.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3432/greenacres/p3080005.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3432/greenacres/p3080004.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3432/greenacres/p3080007.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3432/greenacres/p3080009.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3432/greenacres/p3080010.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3432/greenacres/p3080008.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3432/greenacres/p3080014.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3432/greenacres/p3080016.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3432/greenacres/p3080015.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3432/greenacres/p3080017.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3432/greenacres/p3080018.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3432/greenacres/p3080019.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="14"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3432/greenacres/p3080020.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="15"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3432/greenacres/parking.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="16"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3432/greenacres/vista2.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="17"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3432/greenacres/vista1.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="18"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3432/greenacres/vista3.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="19"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3432/greenacres/vista4.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>VmB002</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>159000</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>old</habitat>
    <latitude>38.85385860</latitude>
    <longitude>0.01089300</longitude>
    <mandate_number>VmB002</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[ADOSADO]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[ADOSADO]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[ADOSADO]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[ADOSADO]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[ADOSADO]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[New Development of Townhouses in Els Poblets, very quiet area and just 600 meters from the first line of the beach. 900 meters from the town of Els poblets, Alicante, Costa Blanca, but very close to all amenities. Different distributions according to model of townhouse. Distribution all on one floor: Living room, open kitchen, 3 bedrooms one with bathroom en suite and 1 bathroom. Distribution two floors: Ground floor open kitchen, living room, master bedroom with bathroom en suite, covered terrace, with the possibility of being glazed in the future. Total 90 m2 approximately. Good construction materials, stoneware floors, pvc windows with double acrsitalamiento, pre-installation air conditioning cold heat, private plot 120 m2 according to model, with private garden, communal area with garden and pool.]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[Nueva Promoción de Adosados en Els Poblets, zona muy tranquila y a escasos 600 metros de la primera línea de playa. A 900 metros del casco urbano de Els poblets, Alicante, Costa Blanca, pero muy cerca de todas las comodidades. Diferentes distribuciones según modelo de adosado. Distribución todo en una planta: Salón comedor, cocina abierta, 3 dormitorios uno con baño en suite y 1 baño completo. Distribución dos plantas: Planta baja cocina abierta, salón comedor, dormitorio principal con baño en suite, terraza cubierta, con posibilidad de ser acristalada en el futuro. Total 90 m2 aproximadamente. Buenos materiales de construcción, suelos de gres, ventanas pvc con doble acrsitalamiento, preinstalación aire acondicionado frio calor,  parcela privativa 120 m2  según  modelo, con jardín privado, zona comunitaria con jardín y piscina.]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[Nouvelle Promotion de Villas à Calpe, quartier très calme et à seulement 600 mètres de la plage. À 900 mètres de la ville de Els Poblets, Alicante, Costa Blanca, mais très proche de toutes les commodités. Les différentes distributions selon le modèle en annexe. Distribution sur un seul étage: Séjour, cuisine, 3 chambres dont une avec salle de bains et 1 salle de bain. Distribution à deux niveaux: rez de chaussée cuisine, salon, chambre principale avec salle de bains, terrasse couverte, avec la possibilité de verre à l&#39;avenir. Au total 90 m2 environ. De bons matériaux de construction, les planchers en céramique, fenêtres en PVC avec double acrsitalamiento, la climatisation et le chauffage de préinstallation, terrain privé de 120 m2 selon le modèle, avec jardin privé, jardin commun et piscine.]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Neue Förderung von Villen in Calpe, sehr ruhig gelegen und nur 600 Meter vom Strand entfernt. 900 Meter von der Stadt Els Poblets, Alicante, Costa Blanca, aber sehr nah an allen Annehmlichkeiten. Verschiedene Verteilungen gemäß angebracht Modell. Verteilung auf einer Etage: Wohnzimmer, Küche, 3 Schlafzimmer, eines mit eigenem Bad und 1 Badezimmer. Aufteilung zwei Etagen: im Erdgeschoss Küche, Wohnzimmer, Schlafzimmer mit Bad, überdachter Terrasse, mit der Möglichkeit von Glas in der Zukunft. Insgesamt 90 m2 ungefähr. Gute Baustoffe, Keramikböden, PVC-Fenster mit Doppel acrsitalamiento, Vorinstallation Klimaanlage und Heizung, eigenes Grundstück 120 m2, je nach Modell, mit eigenem Garten, Gemeinschaftsgarten und Pool.]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[Nuova promozione di ville a Calpe, zona molto tranquilla ea soli 600 metri dalla spiaggia. A 900 metri dal centro di Els Poblets, Alicante, Costa Blanca, ma molto vicino a tutti i servizi. Diverse distribuzioni secondo il modello allegato. Distribuzione tutto su un unico piano: soggiorno, cucina, 3 camere da letto di cui una con bagno privato e 1 bagno. Distribuzione due piani: al piano terra cucina, soggiorno, camera matrimoniale con bagno privato, terrazza coperta, con la possibilità di vetro in futuro. Totale 90 m2 circa. materiali di buona costruzione, pavimenti in ceramica, finestre in PVC con doppi acrsitalamiento, preinstallazione di aria condizionata e riscaldamento, terreno privato di 120 m2 a seconda del modello, con giardino privato, giardino e piscina.]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>86</h_surface>
    <l_surface>120</l_surface>
    <n_beds>3</n_beds>
    <n_baths>2</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>0</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4019/greenacres/596f3ad013111_infografia2.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4019/greenacres/596f3ad471e8b_infografia3.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4019/greenacres/596f3ad696a11_infografia1.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4019/greenacres/planogeneral.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4019/greenacres/vivienda1.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4019/greenacres/vivienda5a.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4019/greenacres/vivienda5b.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4019/greenacres/vivienda5c.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4019/greenacres/vivienda5d.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4019/greenacres/vivienda5e.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4019/greenacres/vivienda5f.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4019/greenacres/vivienda7a.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4019/greenacres/vivienda8a.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="14"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4019/greenacres/vivienda8b.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="15"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4019/greenacres/vivienda8c.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="16"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4019/greenacres/vivienda8d.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="17"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4019/greenacres/vivienda8e.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="18"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/4019/greenacres/vivienda8f.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>B393</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>149900</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>old</habitat>
    <latitude>38.86110407</latitude>
    <longitude>0.02628632</longitude>
    <mandate_number>B393</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[TERRACED HOUSE]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[ADOSADO]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[MAISON MITOYENNE]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[REIHENHAUS]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[CASA A SCHIERA]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[FIRST LINE. Townhouse in quiet, situated in first line. Townhouse duplex close to the beach and all services. Terrace, garden and swimming pool. Apartment of 2 bedrooms (from the bedroom main has views to the sea), 1 bathroom and 1 toilet, lounge dining room, kitchen American. First qualities (Windows PVC, double glazing, railings, garage community). Contact us without obligation.]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[PRIMERA LÍNEA. Adosado en urbanización tranquila, situada en primera línea. Adosado dúplex cercano a la playa así como de todos los servicios. Amplia terraza, jardín y piscina comunitaria.Apartamento de 2 dormitorios (desde el dormitorio principal tiene vistas al mar),1 baño y 1 aseo ,salón comedor, cocina americana. Primeras calidades(ventanas PVC , doble acristalamiento, rejas, garaje comunitario).Consúltenos sin compromiso.]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[PREMIÈRE LIGNE. Maison de ville dans une urbanisation tranquille, situé en première ligne. Maison de ville duplex à proximité de la plage et de tous les services. Terrasse, jardin et piscine. Appartement de 2 chambres à coucher (de la chambre à coucher principale a vues à la mer), 1 salle de bain et 1 toilette, salon salle à manger, cuisine américaine. Qualités premières (fenêtres PVC, double vitrage, balustrades, communauté de garage). Contactez-nous sans obligation.]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[ERSTE ZEILE. Reihenhaus in ruhiger, Urbanisation befindet sich in erster Linie. Freistehende Maisonette nahe am Strand sowie ab all jene Dienstleistungen. Große Terrasse, Garten und Pool Gemeinschaft. Wohnung 2 Schlafzimmer (vom Schlafzimmer Main hat Blick auf das Meer), 1 Badezimmer und 1 WC, Esszimmer, amerikanische Küche lounge. Ersten Qualitäten (Fenster PVC, Doppelverglasung, Geländer, Garage Gemeinschaft). Fragen Sie uns unverbindlich.]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[PRIMA RIGA. Casa a schiera in zona tranquilla, situato in prima linea. Duplex indipendente vicino alla spiaggia, così come di tutti quei servizi. Terrazza, giardino e piscina. 2 camere da letto (dalla camera padronale ha vista sul mare), 1 bagno e 1 WC, soggiorno, angolo cottura. Prima qualità (finestre in PVC, doppi vetri, inferriate, comunità garage). Contattaci senza impegno.]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>70</h_surface>
    <n_beds>2</n_beds>
    <n_baths>1</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>0</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1974/greenacres/p4300093.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1974/greenacres/p4300097.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1974/greenacres/p4300082.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1974/greenacres/p4300081.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1974/greenacres/p4300084.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1974/greenacres/p4300083.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1974/greenacres/p4300086.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1974/greenacres/p4300085.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1974/greenacres/p4300088.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1974/greenacres/p4300089.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1974/greenacres/p4300090.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1974/greenacres/p4300087.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1974/greenacres/p4300091.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="14"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1974/greenacres/p4300092.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="15"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1974/greenacres/p4300094.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="16"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1974/greenacres/p4300096.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="17"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1974/greenacres/p4300095.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>A284</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>129000</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>appartement</habitat>
    <latitude>38.86549905</latitude>
    <longitude>-0.00901242</longitude>
    <mandate_number>A284</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[Apartamento]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[Apartamento]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[Apartamento]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[Apartamento]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[Apartamento]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[Apartamento cercano a la playa (unos 400 m) y de todos los servicios. Con amplia  terraza y jardín privado así como también piscina comunitaria .Apartamento de 2 dormitorios dobles, 2 baños, salón comedor, muebles, electrodomésticos.  Parking y Trastero . Consúltenos sin compromiso.]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[Apartamento cercano a la playa (unos 400 m) y de todos los servicios. Con amplia  terraza y jardín privado así como también piscina comunitaria .Apartamento de 2 dormitorios dobles, 2 baños, salón comedor, muebles, electrodomésticos.  Parking y Trastero . Consúltenos sin compromiso.]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[Apartamento cercano a la playa (unos 400 m) y de todos los servicios. Con amplia  terraza y jardín privado así como también piscina comunitaria .Apartamento de 2 dormitorios dobles, 2 baños, salón comedor, muebles, electrodomésticos.  Parking y Trastero . Consúltenos sin compromiso.]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Apartamento cercano a la playa (unos 400 m) y de todos los servicios. Con amplia  terraza y jardín privado así como también piscina comunitaria .Apartamento de 2 dormitorios dobles, 2 baños, salón comedor, muebles, electrodomésticos.  Parking y Trastero . Consúltenos sin compromiso.]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[Apartamento cercano a la playa (unos 400 m) y de todos los servicios. Con amplia  terraza y jardín privado así como también piscina comunitaria .Apartamento de 2 dormitorios dobles, 2 baños, salón comedor, muebles, electrodomésticos.  Parking y Trastero . Consúltenos sin compromiso.]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>80</h_surface>
    <n_beds>2</n_beds>
    <n_baths>2</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>1</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1622/greenacres/dsc06583.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1622/greenacres/dsc06560.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1622/greenacres/dsc06561.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1622/greenacres/dsc06559.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1622/greenacres/dsc06562.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1622/greenacres/dsc06564.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1622/greenacres/dsc06563.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1622/greenacres/dsc06566.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1622/greenacres/dsc06565.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1622/greenacres/dsc06568.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1622/greenacres/dsc06567.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1622/greenacres/dsc06569.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1622/greenacres/dsc06570.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="14"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1622/greenacres/dsc06571.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="15"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1622/greenacres/dsc06572.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="16"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1622/greenacres/dsc06573.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="17"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1622/greenacres/dsc06574.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="18"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1622/greenacres/dsc06575.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="19"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1622/greenacres/dsc06576.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="20"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1622/greenacres/dsc06577.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="21"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1622/greenacres/dsc06578.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="22"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1622/greenacres/dsc06580.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="23"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1622/greenacres/dsc06579.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="24"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1622/greenacres/dsc06581.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="25"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1622/greenacres/dsc06582.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="26"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1622/greenacres/dsc06584.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="27"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1622/greenacres/dsc06585.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>VmA003</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>126000</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>appartement</habitat>
    <latitude>38.86638570</latitude>
    <longitude>0.00125750</longitude>
    <mandate_number>VmA003</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[APARTMENT]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[APARTAMENTO]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[APPARTEMENT]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[WOHNUNG]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[APPARTAMENTO]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[Apartment close to the playa(600 m) and serviced (1000 m). With spacious terrace and swimming pool, as well as also community garden. Apartment of 2 bedrooms, 2 bathrooms, living room, kitchen, terrace with view to the garden. First calidades(ventanas aluminio, doble acristalamiento, persianas aluminio, puerta seguridad...)... Garage with storage room. Fully equipped. Contact us without obligation.]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[Nuevo apartamento cercano a la playa(600 m) y de todos los servicios (1000 m). Con amplias terraza y piscina comunitaria, así como también jardín comunitario .Apartamento de 2 dormitorios, 2 baños, salón comedor , cocina independiente, amplia terraza con vista al jardin comunitario. Primeras calidades(ventanas aluminio, doble acristalamiento, persianas aluminio, puerta seguridad...).. Garaje con trastero. Completamente equipado. Consúltenos sin compromiso.]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[Appartement à proximité du playa(600 m) et viabilisé (1000 m). Avec grande terrasse et piscine, ainsi qu’aussi jardin communautaire. Appartement de 2 chambres à coucher, 2 salles de bains, salon, cuisine, terrasse avec vue sur le jardin. Première calidades (doble acristalamiento, persianas aluminio, ventanas aluminio, puerta seguridad...)... Garage avec espace de rangement. Entièrement équipée. Contactez-nous sans obligation.]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Wohnung in der Nähe der playa(600 m) und gewartet (1000 m). Mit Terrasse und Schwimmbad, sowie auch Gemeinschaftsgarten. Wohnung mit 2 Schlafzimmer, 2 Bäder, Wohnzimmer, Küche, Terrasse mit Blick auf den Garten. Ersten Calidades (Ventanas Aluminio, Doble Acristalamiento, Persianas Aluminio Puerta Seguridad...)... Garage mit Abstellraum. Komplett ausgestattet. Kontaktieren Sie uns unverbindlich.]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[Appartamento vicino al playa(600 m) e servizi alberghieri (1000 m). Con spaziosa terrazza e piscina, così come anche giardino comunitario. Appartamento di 2 camere da letto, 2 bagni, soggiorno, cucina, terrazza con vista sul giardino. Prima calidades (ventanas aluminio, doble vetri, persianas aluminio, seguridad puerta...)... Garage con ripostiglio. Completamente attrezzata. Contattaci senza impegno.]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>92</h_surface>
    <n_beds>2</n_beds>
    <n_baths>2</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>0</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3743/greenacres/58f9042cc5290_p1010414.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3743/greenacres/58f903f013b5e_p1010403.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3743/greenacres/58f903f494264_p1010405.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3743/greenacres/58f903fb00c15_p1010406.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3743/greenacres/58f903fc9f9b7_p1010404.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3743/greenacres/58f90406a150d_p1010407.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3743/greenacres/58f9040ac936c_p1010409.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3743/greenacres/58f9040eea156_p1010410.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3743/greenacres/58f90412af8b8_p1010411.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3743/greenacres/58f90416306ea_p1010412.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3743/greenacres/58f90417d0dc9_p1010408.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3743/greenacres/58f9041f009c2_p1010413.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3743/greenacres/58f90426008af_p1010415.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="14"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3743/greenacres/58f9043566305_p1010417.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="15"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3743/greenacres/58f9043571d1a_p1010416.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="16"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3743/greenacres/58f9043cd263d_p1010418.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="17"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3743/greenacres/58f904440d848_p1010420.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="18"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3743/greenacres/58f904446efd7_p1010419.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="19"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3743/greenacres/58f9044a22371_p1010421.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="20"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3743/greenacres/58f9045250061_p1010423.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="21"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3743/greenacres/58f9045456e74_p1010422.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="22"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3743/greenacres/58f90458d7557_p1010424.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="23"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3743/greenacres/58f9045bbb9ba_p1010425.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>H482</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>229900</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>luxury</habitat>
    <latitude>38.86072030</latitude>
    <longitude>0.01366460</longitude>
    <mandate_number>H482</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[Cottage]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[Chalet]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[Chalet]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[Ferienhaus]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[Cottage]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[OPPORTUNITY CHALET. Villa on a corner plot of 640 m2 close to the playa(400 m) and all the services (800 m). With spacious terrace and private pool, as well as also garden. Villa with 2 bedrooms with air conditioning cold/heat, 1 bathroom, living room, kitchen,. First quality (windows aluminum tilt and turn, double glazing, central heating, domestic hot water by solar system, parking covered with automatic door semifurnished...). Contact us without obligation]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[Chalet en parcela esquinera de 640 m2 cercano a la playa(400 m) y de todos los servicios (800 m). Con amplias terraza y piscina privada, así como también jardín. Chalet de 2 dormitorios con aire acondicionado frio/calor, 1 baño, salón comedor , cocina equipada, . Primeras calidades(ventanas aluminio oscilobatiente, doble acristalamiento, calefacción central, agua sanitaria por sistema solar, parking cubierto con puerta automática semiamueblado...).Consúltenos sin compromiso]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[CHALET D’OCCASION. Villa dans le coin de la parcelle de 640 m2 à proximité de la playa(400 m) et de tous les services (800 m). Avec grande terrasse et piscine privée, jardin aussi bien ainsi. Villa avec 2 chambres avec air conditionné froid/chaud, 1 salle de bain, salon, cuisine. 1ère qualité (fenêtres aluminium oscillo, double vitrage, chauffage central, eau chaude sanitaire par système solaire, parking couvert avec porte automatique semifurnished...). Contactez-nous sans engagement]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[GELEGENHEIT-CHALET. Villa auf einem Eckgrundstück von 640 m2 in der Nähe der playa(400 m) und alle Dienstleistungen (800 m). Als auch mit Terrasse und privatem Pool Garten. Villa 2 Schlafzimmer mit Klimaanlage kalt / erhitzen, 1 Bad, Wohnzimmer, Esszimmer, Küche,. Erste Qualität (Windows Aluminium kippen und drehen, Isolierverglasung, Zentralheizung, Warmwasser durch Solaranlage,... mit automatischer Tür semifurnished überdachte Parkplätze). Kontaktieren Sie uns unverbindlich]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[CHALET DI OPPORTUNITÀ. Villa su un terreno di angolo di 640 m2 vicino il playa(400 m) e tutti i servizi (800 m). Con spaziosa terrazza e piscina privata, così come anche giardino. Villa con 2 camere da letto con aria condizionata freddo/caldo, 1 bagno, soggiorno, cucina. Prima qualità (windows alluminio ribalta, vetri doppi, riscaldamento centralizzato, acqua calda sanitaria dal sistema solare, parcheggio coperto con porta automatica semiarredata...). Contattaci senza impegno]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>80</h_surface>
    <n_beds>2</n_beds>
    <n_baths>1</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>1</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3398/greenacres/58ebb47e5e4a5_p8260426.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3398/greenacres/58ebb45fc4317_p8260416.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3398/greenacres/58ebb46854507_p8260417.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3398/greenacres/58ebb46b7c88d_p8260421.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3398/greenacres/58ebb46f3e3ac_p8260422.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3398/greenacres/58ebb47252b86_p8260423.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3398/greenacres/58ebb472d41ca_p8260420.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3398/greenacres/58ebb47985362_p8260424.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3398/greenacres/58ebb47e3a273_p8260425.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3398/greenacres/58ebb4841750f_p8260428.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3398/greenacres/58ebb48a502eb_p8260427.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3398/greenacres/58ebb48a87c5d_p8260429.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3398/greenacres/58ebb48f945c3_p8260430.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>VmA001</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>149900</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>appartement</habitat>
    <latitude>38.85478800</latitude>
    <longitude>0.01727410</longitude>
    <mandate_number>VmA001</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[APARTAMENTO]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[APARTAMENTO]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[APARTAMENTO]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[APARTAMENTO]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[APARTAMENTO]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[First floor apartment in complex consisting of seven villas with high apartment and low in the town of Els Poblets, 800 m from the beach, near Denia and Oliva, as well as of all the services. Location very quiet, very clear and beautiful urbanization and mountain views. Conservation excellent condition built in 2005. Fully furnished with appliances included. Square garage on surface. Terrace of 25 square meters. Heated floor, air heating cooling pump, fans on roof of mosquito nets in windows, screens in both bathrooms, rooms, bars on windows and terrace. Canopy windscreen on terrace. Contact us without obligation]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[Fantastico apartamento en primera planta en urbanización compuesta por siete chalets con apartamento alto y bajo en la población de Els Poblets, a 800 m de la playa, muy cerca de Denia y de Oliva, asi como tambien de todos los servicios. Emplazamiento muy tranquilo, vistas muy despejadas y bonitas a la urbanización y a la montaña. Excelente estado de conservación construido en el 2005. Completamente amueblado con electrodomésticos incluidos. Plaza de garaje en superficie. Terraza de 25 metros cuadrados. Calefacción por suelo radiante, bomba de aire frio calor, ventiladores en techo de habitaciones, mosquiteras en ventanas, mámparas en ambos baños, rejas en ventanas y salida a terraza. Toldo antiviento en terraza. Consúltenos sin compromiso]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[Appartement au premier étage dans le complexe composé de sept villas avec appartement haute et basse dans la ville d’Els Poblets, à 800 m de la plage, près de Denia et Oliva, ainsi que de tous les services. Endroit très calmes, très clairs et belles urbanisation et montagne vues. Excellent état de conservation construit en 2005. Entièrement meublée et équipée inclus. Garage carré sur la surface. Terrasse de 25 m². Plancher chauffant, chauffage refroidissement pompe à air, ventilateurs sur le toit des moustiquaires dans les fenêtres, écrans dans les deux salles de bain, chambres, bars sur les fenêtres et terrasse. Pare-brise d’auvent sur terrasse. Contactez-nous sans engagement]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Apartment im ersten Stock im Komplex, bestehend aus sieben Villen mit hohem und niedrigen in der Stadt von Els Poblets, 800 m vom Strand entfernt, in der Nähe von Denia und Oliva, sowie alle Dienstleistungen. Lage sehr ruhig, sehr klar und schön Urbanisierung und Berg Blick. Erhaltung sehr guter Zustand, Baujahr 2005. Voll möbliert mit Geräte enthalten. Quadratmeter Garage auf Oberfläche. Terrasse von 25 Quadratmetern. Fußbodenheizung, kühlende Luft-Wärmepumpe, Fans auf Dach von Moskitonetzen in Windows, Bildschirme in beiden Badezimmern, Zimmer, Bars am Fenster und Terrasse. Vordach Windschutz auf der Terrasse. Kontaktieren Sie uns unverbindlich]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[Appartamento al primo piano in complesso che consiste di sette ville con appartamento alta e bassa nella città di Els Poblets, 800 m dalla spiaggia, vicino a Denia e Oliva, come pure di tutti i servizi. Posizione molto tranquilla, molto chiara e bella vista di urbanizzazione e montagna. Ottime condizioni di conservazione costruito nel 2005. Completamente arredato con elettrodomestici inclusi. Box quadrato sulla superficie. Terrazza di 25 mq. Riscaldamento a pavimento, pompa di raffreddamento riscaldamento aria, ventilatori sul tetto di zanzariere nelle finestre, schermi in bagni, camere, bar sulle finestre e terrazza. Parabrezza di baldacchino sulla terrazza. Contattaci senza impegno]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>105</h_surface>
    <n_beds>2</n_beds>
    <n_baths>2</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>1</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3585/greenacres/img20170319103911.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3585/greenacres/fachada.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3585/greenacres/img20160323113706.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3585/greenacres/img20160323113728.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3585/greenacres/img20160323113757.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3585/greenacres/img20160323113803.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3585/greenacres/img20160323113828.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3585/greenacres/img20160323120927.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3585/greenacres/img20160323120941.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3585/greenacres/img20160323113750.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3585/greenacres/img20160323121003.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3585/greenacres/img20160323121046.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3585/greenacres/img20160323121137.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="14"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3585/greenacres/img20160323121057.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="15"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3585/greenacres/img20160323121308.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="16"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3585/greenacres/img20160323121316.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="17"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3585/greenacres/img20160323121557.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="18"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3585/greenacres/img20160323121614.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="19"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3585/greenacres/img20160323121640.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="20"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3585/greenacres/img20160323121645.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="21"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3585/greenacres/img20160323121652.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="22"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3585/greenacres/img20170319104637.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="23"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3585/greenacres/urbanizacion.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="24"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3585/greenacres/urbanizacion2.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>A353</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>107000</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>appartement</habitat>
    <latitude>38.86506090</latitude>
    <longitude>-0.00753000</longitude>
    <mandate_number>A353</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[APARTMENT]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[APARTAMENTO]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[APPARTEMENT]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[WOHNUNG]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[APPARTAMENTO]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[2 bedroom apartment for sale in the town of Denia, just 9 km away from Denia and 400 from beach.
Housing distributed in 2 bedrooms, two spacious bathroom, living/dining room, equipped kitchen and spacious terraces. The apartment has air conditioning (cold and heat) in bedrooms and living room, PVC Windows with double glass, lined wardrobes and satellite connection. Sold with furniture.
Urbanization with garden, paddle ypiscina community. The property includes garage and storeroom.
Sunny and comfortable housing for long periods of time. Contact us without obligation.]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[Moderno apartamento de 2 dormitorios en venta en el municipio de Denia, a tan sólo 9 km. de Denia y 400 de playa.
Vivienda distribuida en 2 dormitorios, dos amplios baño, salón-comedor, cocina independiente equipada y  amplias terrazas. El apartamento dispone de aparatos de aire acondicionado (frío y calor) en dormitorios y salón comedor, ventanas de PVC con doble cristal, armarios empotrados forrados y conexión satélite. Se vende con muebles.
Urbanización con jardín, paddel  ypiscina comunitarios. La vivienda incluye plaza de garaje y trastero.
Una vivienda cómoda y soleada para disfrutar de largas temporadas. Consúltenos sin compromiso.]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[Appartement de 2 chambres à vendre à la ville de Denia, à seulement 9 km de Denia et 400 de la plage.
Logements répartis en 2 chambres à coucher, deux salles de bains spacieuses, salon/salle à manger, cuisine équipée et terrasses spacieuses. L’appartement dispose de la climatisation (froid et chaleur) dans les chambres et salon, fenêtres en PVC avec double vitrage, placards, bordé connexion satellite. Vendu avec mobilier.
Urbanisation avec jardin, paddle ypiscina communauté. La propriété comprend garage et cellier.
Logement ensoleillé et confortable pendant de longues périodes de temps. Contactez-nous sans obligation.]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[2-Zimmer-Wohnung zum Verkauf in der Stadt Denia, nur 9 km entfernt von Denia und 400 vom Strand entfernt.
Gehäuse in 2 Schlafzimmer, zwei Badezimmer, Wohn-/Esszimmer, ausgestattete Küche und großzügigen Terrassen verteilt. Die Wohnung verfügt über Klimaanlage (Kälte und Wärme) in den Schlafzimmern und Wohnzimmer, PVC-Fenster mit Doppelverglasung, gefüttert, Schränke und Sat-Anschluss. Mit Möbeln verkauft.
Wohnsiedlung mit Garten, Paddel Ypiscina Gemeinschaft. Das Anwesen umfasst Garage und Abstellraum.
Sonnige und komfortable Wohnung für längere Zeit. Kontaktieren Sie uns unverbindlich.]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[Appartamento di 2 camere da letto in vendita nella città di Denia, a soli 9 km lontano da Denia e 400 dalla spiaggia.
Alloggi distribuiti in 2 camere da letto, due bagni spaziosi, soggiorno/sala da pranzo, cucina attrezzata e ampie terrazze. L&#39;appartamento dispone di aria condizionata (freddo e caldo) nelle camere da letto e soggiorno, finestre in PVC con doppio vetro, foderato armadi e collegamento satellitare. Venduto con mobili.
Complesso residenziale con giardino, paddle ypiscina comunità. La proprietà comprende garage e ripostiglio.
Soleggiato e confortevole alloggio per lunghi periodi di tempo. Contattaci senza impegno.]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>70</h_surface>
    <n_beds>2</n_beds>
    <n_baths>2</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>1</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3688/greenacres/45955121.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3688/greenacres/45955131.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3688/greenacres/45955141.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3688/greenacres/45955151.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3688/greenacres/45955161.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3688/greenacres/dsc01655.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3688/greenacres/dsc01666.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3688/greenacres/dsc01669.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3688/greenacres/dsc01674.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3688/greenacres/dsc01675.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3688/greenacres/lastscan1.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3688/greenacres/p1000799.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3688/greenacres/p1000805.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="14"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3688/greenacres/p1000813.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="15"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3688/greenacres/p1000815.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="16"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3688/greenacres/p1000811.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="17"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3688/greenacres/p1000821.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="18"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3688/greenacres/p1000848.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="19"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3688/greenacres/p1000830.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>B401</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>154500</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>old</habitat>
    <latitude>38.85997040</latitude>
    <longitude>-0.00218210</longitude>
    <mandate_number>B401</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[TERRACED HOUSE]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[ADOSADO]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[MAISON MITOYENNE]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[REIHENHAUS]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[CASA A SCHIERA]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[Townhouse duplex with 3 bedrooms for sale in the municipality of Vergel, only 9 km. away from Denia and 1 kms. Beach.
Housing in 2 plants distributed in 3 bedrooms, a spacious bathroom with shower, a bathroom, living/dining room with access to the common areas, kitchen independent equipped and spacious front terrace with exit to the swimming pool. Private garden and bbq. The cottage has air-conditioning (hot and cold) devices, PVC Windows with double glazing, armoured door, lined wardrobes. Sold with furniture.
 It consists of a community garden and swimming pool. 
 Sunny and comfortable housing for long periods of time. Contact us without obligation]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[OPORTUNIDAD. Adosado dúplex de 3 dormitorios en venta en el municipio de Vergel, a tan sólo 9 km. de Denia y 1 kms. de playa.
Vivienda en 2 plantas distribuida en 3 dormitorios, un baño amplio con ducha, un baño, salón-comedor con salida a las zonas comunes, cocina independiente equipada y  amplia terraza  delantera con salida a la piscina. Jardín privado y bbq. El adosado dispone de aparatos de aire acondicionado (frío y calor), ventanas de PVC con doble cristal, puerta blindada, armarios empotrados forrados. Se vende con muebles.
 Consta de jardín y piscina comunitarios. 
 Una vivienda cómoda y soleada para disfrutar de largas temporadas. Consúltenos sin compromiso]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[Maison de ville duplex avec 3 chambres à vendre à la municipalité de Vergel, à seulement 9 km de Denia et à 1 km. Plage.
Logement dans 2 usines réparties dans 3 chambres, une salle de bain avec douche, une salle de bains, salon/salle à manger avec accès aux zones communes, indépendantes avant équipée et spacieuse cuisine terrasse avec accès à la piscine. Jardin privé et bbq. Le gîte dispose d’air conditionné (chaud et froid) des dispositifs, fenêtres en PVC avec double vitrage, porte blindée, armoires doublés. Vendu avec mobilier.
 Il se compose d’un jardin communautaire et une piscine. 
 Logement ensoleillé et confortable pendant de longues périodes de temps. Contactez-nous sans engagement]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Stadthaus mit 3 Schlafzimmern zum Verkauf in der Gemeinde Vergel, nur 9 km entfernt von Denia und 1 km duplex. Strand.
Gehäuse in 2 Pflanzen verteilt in 3 Schlafzimmer, ein geräumiges Badezimmer mit Dusche, Bad, Wohn-/Esszimmer mit Zugang zu den öffentlichen Bereichen, unabhängige ausgestattete und geräumige Front Küche Terrasse mit Ausgang zum Pool. Privater Garten und Bbq. Das Ferienhaus verfügt über Klimaanlage (warm / kalt) Geräte, PVC-Fenster mit doppelter Verglasung, gepanzerte Tür, gefütterte Schränke. Mit Möbeln verkauft.
 Es besteht aus einem Gemeinschaftsgarten und Pool. 
 Sonnige und komfortable Wohnung für längere Zeit. Kontaktieren Sie uns unverbindlich]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[Casa a schiera su due piani con 3 camere da letto in vendita nel comune di Vergel, solo 9 km lontano da Denia e a 1 km. Spiaggia.
Alloggio in 2 impianti distribuiti in 3 camere da letto, un ampio bagno con doccia, un bagno, soggiorno/sala da pranzo con accesso alla zona comune, fronte cucina indipendente attrezzata e spaziosa terrazza con uscita a bordo piscina. Giardino privato e barbecue. Il cottage ha aria condizionata (calda e fredda) dispositivi, finestre in PVC con doppi vetri, porta blindata, armadi interno foderati. Venduto con mobili.
 Si compone di una comunità giardino e piscina. 
 Soleggiato e confortevole alloggio per lunghi periodi di tempo. Contattaci senza impegno]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>92</h_surface>
    <n_beds>3</n_beds>
    <n_baths>2</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>1</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3695/greenacres/58ec924a4e326_b4010000g.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3695/greenacres/p1310059.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3695/greenacres/p1310062.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3695/greenacres/p1310063.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3695/greenacres/p1310066.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3695/greenacres/p1310061.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3695/greenacres/p1310068.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3695/greenacres/p1310069.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3695/greenacres/p1310071.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3695/greenacres/p1310072.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3695/greenacres/p1310070.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3695/greenacres/p1310076.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3695/greenacres/p1310081.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="14"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3695/greenacres/p1310077.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="15"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3695/greenacres/p1310082.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="16"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3695/greenacres/p1310083.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="17"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3695/greenacres/p1310089.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="18"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3695/greenacres/p1310090.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>H544</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>279990</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>luxury</habitat>
    <latitude>38.86065490</latitude>
    <longitude>0.01362040</longitude>
    <mandate_number>H544</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[COTTAGE]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[CHALET]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[CHALET]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[FERIENHAUS]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[COTTAGE]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[Fantastico chalet a 300 metros de la playa, renovado recientemente. 2 dormitorios dobles, con posibilidad de 3, salón comedor con chimenea, gran terraza cubierta acristalada, piscina, garaje, trasteros. Aire acondicionado frío/calor, muebles y electrodomésticos.  Consúltenos sin compromiso]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[Fantastico chalet a 300 metros de la playa, renovado recientemente. 2 dormitorios dobles, con posibilidad de 3, salón comedor con chimenea, gran terraza cubierta acristalada, piscina, garaje, trasteros. Aire acondicionado frío/calor, muebles y electrodomésticos.  Consúltenos sin compromiso]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[Fantastico chalet a 300 metros de la playa, renovado recientemente. 2 dormitorios dobles, con posibilidad de 3, salón comedor con chimenea, gran terraza cubierta acristalada, piscina, garaje, trasteros. Aire acondicionado frío/calor, muebles y electrodomésticos.  Consúltenos sin compromiso]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Fantastico chalet a 300 metros de la playa, renovado recientemente. 2 dormitorios dobles, con posibilidad de 3, salón comedor con chimenea, gran terraza cubierta acristalada, piscina, garaje, trasteros. Aire acondicionado frío/calor, muebles y electrodomésticos.  Consúltenos sin compromiso]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[Fantastico chalet a 300 metros de la playa, renovado recientemente. 2 dormitorios dobles, con posibilidad de 3, salón comedor con chimenea, gran terraza cubierta acristalada, piscina, garaje, trasteros. Aire acondicionado frío/calor, muebles y electrodomésticos.  Consúltenos sin compromiso]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>120</h_surface>
    <l_surface>400</l_surface>
    <n_beds>2</n_beds>
    <n_baths>1</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>0</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3811/greenacres/p7180086.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3811/greenacres/p7180066.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3811/greenacres/p7180067.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3811/greenacres/p7180070.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3811/greenacres/p7180069.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3811/greenacres/p7180071.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3811/greenacres/p7180073.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3811/greenacres/p7180072.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3811/greenacres/p7180075.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3811/greenacres/p7180077.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3811/greenacres/p7180076.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3811/greenacres/p7180078.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3811/greenacres/p7180080.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="14"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3811/greenacres/p7180079.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="15"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3811/greenacres/p7180081.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="16"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3811/greenacres/p7180082.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="17"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3811/greenacres/p7180083.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="18"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3811/greenacres/p7180084.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="19"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3811/greenacres/p7180085.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="20"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3811/greenacres/p7180087.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="21"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3811/greenacres/p7180089.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>A348</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>225000</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>appartement</habitat>
    <latitude>38.84665430</latitude>
    <longitude>0.08869480</longitude>
    <mandate_number>A348</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[APARTMENT]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[APARTAMENTO]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[APPARTEMENT]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[WOHNUNG]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[APPARTAMENTO]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[Luxury second floor apartment in the town of Denia, 100 m from the beach, close to Denia and Oliva, as well as all the services. Location very quiet, very clear and beautiful views of the estate. Conservation excellent condition built in 2002.  Two bedrooms and two bathrooms.  Kitchen, fully furnished with appliances included, terrace, air heating cooling pump. Contact us without obligation]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[Lujoso apartamento en segunda  planta en la población de Denia, a 100 m de la playa, muy cerca de Denia y de Oliva, así como también de todos los servicios. Emplazamiento muy tranquilo, vistas muy despejadas y bonitas a la urbanización. Excelente estado de conservación construido en el 2002.  Dos dormitorios y dos baños.  Cocina equipada, completamente amueblado con electrodomésticos incluidos, Terraza, bomba de aire frio calor. Consúltenos sin compromiso]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[Luxueux appartement au deuxième étage dans la ville de Denia, à 100 m de la plage, près de Denia et Oliva, ainsi que tous les services. Endroit très calme, très clair et belle vue de la succession. Excellent état de conservation construit en 2002.  Deux chambres et deux salles de bains.  Cuisine, totalement équipée avec appareils inclus, terrasse, chauffage pompe à refroidissement à air. Contactez-nous sans engagement]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Luxuswohnung im zweiten Stock der Stadt Denia, 100 m vom Strand entfernt, in der Nähe von Denia und Oliva, sowie alle Dienstleistungen. Lage sehr ruhig, sehr klar und schön Blick auf das Anwesen. Erhaltung sehr guter Zustand, Baujahr 2002.  Zwei Schlafzimmer und zwei Bäder.  Küche, voll möbliert mit Geräte enthalten, Terrasse, Luftheizung Kühlpumpe. Kontaktieren Sie uns unverbindlich]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[Appartamento al piano secondo di lusso nella città di Denia, a 100 m dalla spiaggia, vicino a Denia e Oliva, nonché tutti i servizi. Posizione molto tranquilla, molto chiara e bella vista sulla tenuta. Ottime condizioni di conservazione costruito nel 2002.  Due camere da letto e due bagni.  Cucina, completamente arredata con elettrodomestici inclusi, terrazza, riscaldamento pompa di raffreddamento ad aria. Contattaci senza impegno]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>90</h_surface>
    <n_beds>2</n_beds>
    <n_baths>2</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>1</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3692/greenacres/p7180065.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3692/greenacres/p7180033.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3692/greenacres/p7180034.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3692/greenacres/p7180038.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3692/greenacres/p7180039.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3692/greenacres/p7180042.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3692/greenacres/p7180040.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3692/greenacres/p7180043.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3692/greenacres/p7180046.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3692/greenacres/p7180044.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3692/greenacres/p7180047.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3692/greenacres/p7180048.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3692/greenacres/p7180051.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="14"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3692/greenacres/p7180052.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="15"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3692/greenacres/p7180054.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="16"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3692/greenacres/p7180055.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="17"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3692/greenacres/p7180056.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="18"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3692/greenacres/p7180057.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="19"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3692/greenacres/p7180058.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="20"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3692/greenacres/p7180061.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="21"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3692/greenacres/p7180063.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="22"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3692/greenacres/p7180064.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="23"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3692/greenacres/p7180060.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>B373</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>185000</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>old</habitat>
    <latitude>38.85804716</latitude>
    <longitude>0.00143746</longitude>
    <mandate_number>B373</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[ADOSADO]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[ADOSADO]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[ADOSADO]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[ADOSADO]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[ADOSADO]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[Terraced house semi-detached. Very close to the beach (400m) as well as all the services. Large terrace and garden, easy maintenance. It consists of 3 bedrooms, 2 bathrooms, 2 toilets, dining room, kitchen. First qualities (windows and blinds PVC, bars, double glazing, door armoured, fireplace cassete, pump cold heat...) Furniture and appliances included. Contact us without obligation]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[Adosado Pareado. Muy cercano a la playa (400m) así como de todos los servicios. Amplia terraza y jardín privado, de muy facil mantenimiento. Consta de 3 dormitorios, 2 baños, 2 aseos, salón comedor, cocina independiente,  lavadero, gran sotano  80m2. Primeras calidades(ventanas y persianas PVC,  rejas, doble acristalamiento, puerta blindada,chimenea cassete, bomba frio calor..)Muebles y electrodomésticos incluidos.Consúltenos sin compromiso]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[Maison mitoyenne jumelée. Très proche de la plage (400 m), mais aussi tous les services. Grande terrasse et jardin privé, d’un entretien très facile. Il se compose de 3 chambres, 2 salles de bains, 2 WC, salle à manger, cuisine. Première qualité (fenêtres et stores en PVC, caillebotis, double vitrage, porte blindée, état de la cheminée, pompe à chaleur froid...) Meubles et électroménagers inclus. Consultez-nous sans engagement]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Stadthaus-Couplet. Ganz in der Nähe zum Strand (400 m), sowie alle Dienstleistungen. Große Terrasse und Garten, einfache Wartung. Es besteht aus 3 Schlafzimmer, 2 Badezimmer, 2 WCs, Esszimmer, Küche. Erste Qualität (Windows und PVC-Jalousien, Gitterroste, Doppelverglasung, gepanzerte Tür, Kamin Cassete, kalte Wärmepumpe...) Möbel und Geräte enthalten. Kontaktieren Sie uns unverbindlich]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[Casa a schiera semi-indipendente. Molto vicino alla spiaggia (400 m) così come di tutti quei servizi. Ampio terrazzo e giardino, facile manutenzione. Si compone di 3 camere da letto, 2 bagni, 2 WC, Sala da pranzo, cucina indipendente. Prima qualità (finestre e persiane in PVC, grigliati, vetri doppi, porta blindata, cassete di camino, pompa di calore freddo...) Mobili ed elettrodomestici inclusi. Contattaci senza impegno]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>181</h_surface>
    <n_beds>3</n_beds>
    <n_baths>2</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>1</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050052.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050027.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050026.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050028.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050029.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050032.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050030.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050033.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050035.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050034.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050037.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050036.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050039.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="14"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050040.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="15"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050042.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="16"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050043.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="17"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050041.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="18"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050044.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="19"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050045.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="20"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050047.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="21"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050046.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="22"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050048.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="23"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050049.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="24"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050050.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="25"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050051.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="26"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050054.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="27"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050056.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="28"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050055.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="29"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1630/greenacres/p3050057.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>VmA002</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>145000</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Valencia/València</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>appartement</habitat>
    <latitude>38.89006942</latitude>
    <longitude>-0.04728854</longitude>
    <mandate_number>VmA002</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[Nueva Promoción]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[Nueva Promoción]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[Nueva Promoción]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[Nueva Promoción]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[Nueva Promoción]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[Promotion located 5Km of olive, in the estate of San Fernando, about 150 metres from the beach.  Located in a very quiet, near Oliva (Valencia) and Denia (Alicante) on the Costa Blanca, in the South of the province of Valencia with a magnificent beach of white sand and crystal clear waters. Very close to all amenities of supermarkets, restaurants, Marina, cafes, hotel, golf enclosure Less than 100 km from the airports of Alicante and Valencia. The building consists of 21 apartments distributed in 1st, 2nd, 3rd and penthouses with solarium on the top.  Apartments of 1, 2 and 3 bedrooms with two bathrooms. The kitchen is open to the living room and equipped with furniture ups and downs, ceramic hob, electric oven and Extractor hood.  As well as spacious terraces. Pre-installation of air conditioning in the entire apartment.  The estate consists of a beautiful garden community, swimming pool and area of game child.]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[Promoción situada a 5Km de Oliva, en la urbanización de San Fernando, a unos 150 metros de la playa.  Situada en una zona muy tranquila, cerca de Oliva(Valencia) y Denia(Alicante) en la Costa Blanca, en el sur de la provincia de Valencia con una magnifica playa de arena blanca y aguas cristalinas. Muy cerca de todos los servicios  de supermercados, restaurantes, recinto de deportivo, cafeterías,  hotel, golf, etc. A menos de 100 Km  de los aeropuertos de Alicante y Valencia. El edificio consta de 21 apartamentos distribuidos en 1º,2º, 3º y áticos  con solárium en la parte superior.  Apartamentos de  1, 2 y 3 dormitorios con dos baños. La cocina está abierta al salón  y equipada con muebles altos y bajos, placa vitrocerámica,  horno eléctrico, y campana extractora.  Así como también de amplias terrazas. Preinstalación de aire acondicionado en  todo el apartamento.  La  urbanización consta de  un bonito jardín comunitario, piscina y zona de juego infantil.]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[Promotion situé à 5 Km de l’olive, dans le domaine de San Fernando, à environ 150 mètres de la plage.  Situé dans un très calme, près d’Oliva (Valence) et Denia (Alicante), sur la Costa Blanca, dans le sud de la province de Valence, avec une magnifique plage de sable blanc et limpides eaux. Très proche de toutes commodités, supermarchés, restaurants, cafés, hôtel, Marina, enceinte golf Moins de 100 km des aéroports d’Alicante et Valence. Le bâtiment se compose de 21 appartements répartis en 1ère, 2ème, 3ème et penthouses avec solarium sur le toit.  Appartements de 1, 2 et 3 chambres avec deux salles de bains. La cuisine est ouverte sur le séjour et équipée avec meubles hauts et bas, plaques vitro céramiques, four électrique et hotte aspirante.  Ainsi aussi de spacieuses terrasses. Pré-installation de la climatisation dans tout l’appartement.  Le domaine se compose d’une beau jardin, piscine et aire de jeux pour enfants.]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Förderung liegt 5 Km von Olive, in dem Nachlass von San Fernando, ca. 150 m vom Strand entfernt.  Befindet sich in einer Zone sehr ruhig, in der Nähe von Olive (Valencia) und Denia (Alicante) im Costa weiß, im Süden der Provinz Valencia mit einem herrlichen Strand, der Sand weiß und das Wasser kristallklar. Ganz in der Nähe alle Dienste von Supermärkten, Restaurants, Austragungsort der Sport, Cafés, Hotels, Golf, etc.. Weniger als 100 km von den Flughäfen Alicante und Valencia. Das Gebäude besteht aus 21 Wohnungen im 1., 2., 3. und Penthäuser mit Solarium auf der Oberseite verteilt.  Wohnungen 1, 2 und 3 Schlafzimmer mit zwei Badezimmern. Die Küche ist offen zum Wohnzimmer und ausgestattet mit Möbel hoch und niedrig, Platte-Kochfeld und Backofen Elektro Kampagne Extractor.  Als auch der großzügigen Terrassen. Vor der Installation der Klimaanlage in der Wohnung.  Das Anwesen besteht aus einem schönen Garten, Gemeinschaftspool und Kinderspielplatz.]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[Promozione si trova a 5 Km di oliva, nella tenuta di San Fernando, a circa 150 metri dalla spiaggia.  Situato in una zona molto tranquilla, vicino a Oliva (Valencia) e Denia (Alicante) sulla Costa Blanca, nel sud della provincia di Valencia con una magnifica spiaggia di sabbia bianca e acque cristalline acque. Molto vicino a tutti i servizi di supermercati, ristoranti, caffetterie, hotel, Marina, recinzione golf A meno di 100 Km dagli aeroporti di Alicante e Valencia. L&#39;edificio è costituito da 21 appartamenti distribuiti in 1 °, 2 °, 3 ° e attici con solarium nella parte superior.  Appartamenti di 1, 2 e 3 camere da letto con due bagni. La cucina è aperta sul soggiorno e dotate di mobili alti e Bassi, piano cottura in vetroceramica, forno elettrico e cappa aspirante.  Oltre ad ampie terrazze. Pre-installazione di aria condizionata in tutto l&#39;appartamento.  La tenuta è composta da una bella comunità del giardino, la piscina e la zona di gioco bambino.]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>75</h_surface>
    <n_beds>2</n_beds>
    <n_baths>2</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>0</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1313/greenacres/vitrinacomedor.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1313/greenacres/58079b0d5898f_bao2.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1313/greenacres/58079b0d596cb_baoprincipal.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1313/greenacres/baoprincipal2.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1313/greenacres/cocina.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1313/greenacres/58079b0d5babb_cocina1.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1313/greenacres/58079b0d5d7b1_comedor.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1313/greenacres/dormitorio2.2.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1313/greenacres/58079b0d5f6eb_dormitorio3.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1313/greenacres/58079b0d60292_dormitoriopricipal2.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1313/greenacres/duchadormprincipal.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1313/greenacres/58079b0d62057_dormitorioprincipal.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1313/greenacres/58079b0d6357a_salon.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="14"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1313/greenacres/salon2.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="15"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1313/greenacres/58079b0d65474_saloncomedor.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>A308</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>199500</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>appartement</habitat>
    <latitude>38.86442977</latitude>
    <longitude>-0.00783225</longitude>
    <mandate_number>A308</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[Apartment]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[Apartamento]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[Appartement]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[Wohnung]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[Appartamento]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[PENTHOUSE. Beautiful and spacious penthouse with views to the sea and the mountain, close to the beach (400 metres) and all the services. 100 m2 of terraces, spacious communal green areas and 2 pools community, paddle, playground, BBQ. Apartment with 3 bedrooms, 2 bathrooms, dining room, furniture, appliances. Parking and storage room. Consult us without commitment.]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[ÁTICO.Precioso y amplio ático con vistas al mar y a la montaña,cercano a la playa (unos 400 m) y de todos los servicios. Con 100 m2 de terrazas, amplias zonas verdes comunitarias y 2 piscinas comunitaria, paddle, zona infantil, BBQ .Apartamento de 3 dormitorios, 2 baños, salón comedor, muebles, electrodomésticos. Parking y Trastero. Consúltenos sin compromiso.]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[PENTHOUSE. Beau et spacieux penthouse avec vue sur la mer et la montagne, proche de la plage (400 mètres) et tous les services. Avec 100 m2 de terrasses, vastes espaces verts communautaires et 2 communauté de piscines, paddle, enfant de la région, BBQ. Appartement avec 3 chambres, 2 salles de bain, salle à manger, meubles, appareils électroménagers. Stationnement et le stockage. Contactez-nous sans obligation.]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[PENTHOUSE. Schöne und große Penthouse mit Blick auf das Meer und auf den Berg, nahe dem Strand (ca. 400 m) und alle diese Dienste. 100 m2 Terrassen, geräumige gemeinschaftliche Grünflächen und 2 Pools Gemeinschaft, Paddel, Spielplatz, GRILL. Wohnung mit 3 Schlafzimmer, 2 Bäder, Wohn Esszimmer, Möbel, Haushaltsgeräte. Parkplatz und Abstellraum. Fragen Sie uns unverbindlich.]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[ATTICO. Bellissimo e ampio attico con vista al mare e alla montagna, vicino alla spiaggia (circa 400m) e di tutti i loro servizi. 100 m2 di terrazze, ampi spazi verdi comuni e comunità di 2 piscine, paddle, parco giochi per bambini, Barbecue. Appartamento di 3 camere da letto, 2 bagni, Sala da pranzo, mobili, elettrodomestici. Parcheggio e deposito. Consultateci senza impegno.]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>104</h_surface>
    <n_beds>3</n_beds>
    <n_baths>2</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>1</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1623/greenacres/p7090028.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1623/greenacres/p7090048.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1623/greenacres/p7090022.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1623/greenacres/p7090023.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1623/greenacres/p7090024.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1623/greenacres/p7090025.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1623/greenacres/p7090026.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1623/greenacres/p7090029.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1623/greenacres/p7090030.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1623/greenacres/p7090032.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1623/greenacres/p7090031.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1623/greenacres/p7090033.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1623/greenacres/p7090034.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="14"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1623/greenacres/p7090037.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="15"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1623/greenacres/p7090038.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="16"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1623/greenacres/p7090039.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="17"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1623/greenacres/p7090041.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="18"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1623/greenacres/p7090040.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="19"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1623/greenacres/p7090043.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="20"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1623/greenacres/p7090042.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="21"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1623/greenacres/p7090045.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="22"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1623/greenacres/p7090044.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="23"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1623/greenacres/p7090046.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="24"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1623/greenacres/p7090047.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="25"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1623/greenacres/p7090049.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="26"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1623/greenacres/p7090050.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="27"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1623/greenacres/p7090051.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>H542</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>249000</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>luxury</habitat>
    <latitude>38.84538050</latitude>
    <longitude>0.01049260</longitude>
    <mandate_number>H542</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[COTTAGE]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[CHALET]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[CHALET]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[FERIENHAUS]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[COTTAGE]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[Independent villa with plot of 650 m2. 2 double bedrooms, 2 bathrooms (1 en suite), living room with fireplace, sunroom, air conditioning/heating, swimming pool, storage room, covered parking, PVC Windows, blinds, gates... Furniture and household appliances. Contact us without obligation]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[Chalet independiente con parcela de 650 m2. 2 dormitorios dobles, 2 baños (1 en suite), salón comedor con chimenea, terraza acristalada, aire acondicionado frío/calor, piscina, trastero, parking cubierto, ventanas PVC, persianas, rejas... Muebles y electrodomésticos. Consúltenos sin compromiso]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[Maison indépendante avec terrain de 650 m2. 2 chambres doubles, 2 salles de bains (1 avec salle de bains), salon avec cheminée, véranda, climatisation/chauffage, piscine, salle de stockage, parking, fenêtres en PVC, stores, portails de couvert... Appareils de meubles et de ménage. Consultez-nous sans engagement]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Freistehende Villa mit Grundstück von 650 m2. 2 Doppel-Schlafzimmer, 2 Bäder (1 en-suite), Wohnzimmer mit Kamin, Wintergarten, Klimaanlage/Heizung, Schwimmbad, Abstellraum, überdachter Parkplatz, PVC-Fenster, Jalousien, Tore... Möbel und Haushaltsgeräte. Kontaktieren Sie uns unverbindlich]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[Villa indipendente con terreno di 650 m2. 2 camere matrimoniali, 2 bagni (1 en suite), soggiorno con camino, veranda, aria condizionata, piscina, ripostiglio, parcheggio coperto, finestre in PVC, tapparelle, cancelli,... Mobili ed elettrodomestici. Consultateci senza impegno]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>90</h_surface>
    <n_beds>2</n_beds>
    <n_baths>2</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>0</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1663/greenacres/p6240080.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1663/greenacres/p6240055.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1663/greenacres/p6240056.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1663/greenacres/p6240057.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1663/greenacres/p6240060.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1663/greenacres/p6240059.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1663/greenacres/p6240063.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1663/greenacres/p6240065.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1663/greenacres/p6240067.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1663/greenacres/p6240066.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1663/greenacres/p6240069.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1663/greenacres/p6240070.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1663/greenacres/p6240072.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="14"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1663/greenacres/p6240071.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="15"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1663/greenacres/p6240073.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="16"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1663/greenacres/p6240074.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="17"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1663/greenacres/p6240075.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="18"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1663/greenacres/p6240076.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="19"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1663/greenacres/p6240078.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="20"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1663/greenacres/p6240079.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="21"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1663/greenacres/p6240077.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>H519</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>199500</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>luxury</habitat>
    <latitude>38.86323039</latitude>
    <longitude>-0.00030147</longitude>
    <mandate_number>H519</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[COTTAGE]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[CHALET]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[CHALET]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[FERIENHAUS]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[COTTAGE]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[Villa with 5 years old. Impeccable State. 3 bedrooms double, 2 bathrooms with shower, large lounge dining room, kitchen independent, terrace cover, storage room. Plot of 600 m2. Contact us without obligation.]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[Chalet con 5 años de antigüedad. Impecable estado. 3 dormitorios dobles, 2 baños con ducha, gran salón comedor, cocina independiente, terraza cubierta, trastero. Parcela de 600 m2. Consúltenos sin compromiso.]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[Chalet avec 5 ans d’antiquité. État impeccable. 3 chambres doubles, 2 salles de bains avec douche, grand salon, cuisine, terrasse, débarras. Terrain de 600 m2. Contactez-nous sans obligation.]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Chalet mit 5 Jahren der Antike. Tadelloser Zustand. 3 Doppelzimmer, 2 Bäder mit Dusche, großes Wohnzimmer, Küche, Terrasse, Abstellraum. Grundstück von 600 m2. Kontaktieren Sie uns unverbindlich.]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[Villa con 5 anni di età. Stato impeccabile. 3 camere matrimoniali, 2 bagni con doccia, ampio soggiorno, cucina, terrazza, ripostiglio. Terreno di 600 m2. Contattaci senza impegno.]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>120</h_surface>
    <n_beds>3</n_beds>
    <n_baths>2</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>0</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1691/greenacres/p1290201.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1691/greenacres/p1290185.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1691/greenacres/p1290183.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1691/greenacres/p1290186.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1691/greenacres/p1290188.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1691/greenacres/p1290187.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1691/greenacres/p1290190.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1691/greenacres/p1290189.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1691/greenacres/p1290193.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1691/greenacres/p1290194.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1691/greenacres/p1290192.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1691/greenacres/p1290196.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1691/greenacres/p1290195.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="14"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1691/greenacres/p1290197.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="15"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1691/greenacres/p1290198.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="16"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1691/greenacres/p1290199.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="17"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1691/greenacres/p1290203.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="18"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1691/greenacres/p1290204.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="19"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1691/greenacres/p1290200.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="20"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1691/greenacres/p1290205.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="21"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1691/greenacres/p1290206.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="22"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1691/greenacres/p1290208.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="23"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1691/greenacres/p1290207.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="24"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1691/greenacres/situacin.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>A341</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>110000</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>appartement</habitat>
    <latitude>38.86120660</latitude>
    <longitude>-0.00488450</longitude>
    <mandate_number>A341</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[Apartment]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[Apartamento]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[Appartement]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[Wohnung]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[Appartamento]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[Apartment very close to the beach and of all those services. With spacious terrace and swimming pool and garden community. Apartment with 2 bedrooms, 2 bathrooms, living room, kitchen with Gallery, large terrace. First calidades(ventanas aluminio, doble acristalamiento, persianas aluminio...)... Garage with storage room. . Contact us without obligation.]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[Apartamento  muy cercano  a la playa y de todos los servicios. Con amplias terraza y piscina  y jardín comunitaria.Apartamento de 2 dormitorios, 2 baños, salón comedor, cocina independiente, con galería, amplia terraza . Primeras calidades(ventanas aluminio, doble acristalamiento, persianas aluminio...).. Garaje con trastero. . Consúltenos sin compromiso.]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[Appartement proche de la plage et de tous les services. Avec grande terrasse et piscine et jardin communautaire. Appartement avec 2 chambres à coucher, 2 salles de bains, salon, cuisine avec galerie, grande terrasse. Première calidades (aluminio ventanas, doble acristalamiento, persianas aluminio...)... Garage avec espace de rangement. . Consultez-nous sans engagement.]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Apartment nahe dem Strand und allen Dienstleistungen. Mit Terrasse und Schwimmbad und Gemeinschaftsgarten. Apartment mit 2 Schlafzimmer, 2 Bäder, Wohnzimmer, Küche mit Galerie, große Terrasse. Ersten Calidades (Ventanas Aluminio, Doble Acristalamiento, Persianas Aluminio...)... Garage mit Abstellraum. . Fragen Sie uns unverbindlich.]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[Appartamento molto vicino alla spiaggia e di tutti quei servizi. Con ampia terrazza, piscina e giardino comunitari. Appartamento con 2 camere da letto, 2 bagni, soggiorno, cucina con soppalco, ampia terrazza. Prima calidades (ventanas aluminio, doble vetri, persianas aluminio...)... Garage con ripostiglio. . Consultateci senza impegno.]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>75</h_surface>
    <n_beds>2</n_beds>
    <n_baths>2</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>0</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1973/greenacres/p4110104.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1973/greenacres/p4110103.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1973/greenacres/p4110105.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1973/greenacres/p4110106.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1973/greenacres/p4110108.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1973/greenacres/p4110110.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1973/greenacres/p4110109.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1973/greenacres/p4110111.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1973/greenacres/p4110112.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1973/greenacres/p4110113.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1973/greenacres/p4110115.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1973/greenacres/p4110116.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1973/greenacres/p4110118.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="14"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1973/greenacres/p4110120.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="15"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1973/greenacres/p4110121.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="16"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1973/greenacres/p4110122.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="17"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1973/greenacres/p4110124.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="18"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1973/greenacres/p4110125.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="19"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1973/greenacres/p4110127.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="20"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1973/greenacres/p4110126.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>B394</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>125000</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>old</habitat>
    <latitude>38.85816000</latitude>
    <longitude>0.00006290</longitude>
    <mandate_number>B394</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[TERRACED HOUSE]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[ADOSADO]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[MAISON MITOYENNE]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[REIHENHAUS]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[CASA A SCHIERA]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[Townhouse with private plot in impeccable condition. Terraced house close to the beach (450 m) as well as all the services. Large terrace as well as also has a nice terrace and garden. Apartment with 3 bedrooms, 2 bathrooms, living room with stove cassette, independent kitchen, first quality (Windows of PVC, double glazing and blinds...) Furniture and appliances included. Consult us without commitment.]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[OCASIÓN.Adosado con parcela privada en impecables condiciones.Adosado cercano a la playa (450 m) así como de todos los servicios. Amplia terraza y jardín .Apartamento de 3 dormitorios, 2 baños,salón comedor con estufa cassete, cocina office, Primeras calidades (Ventanas de PVC, climalit, persianas...)Muebles y electrodomésticos incluidos.Consúltenos sin compromiso.]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[Maison de ville avec terrain privé dans un état impeccable. Maison mitoyenne à proximité de la plage (450 m) aussi bien à partir de tous ces services. Grande terrasse a aussi également une jolie terrasse et un jardin. Appartement avec 3 chambres, 2 salles de bains, salon avec poêle à cassette, cuisine indépendante, de première qualité (fenêtres de PVC, double vitrage et stores...) Meubles et électroménagers inclus. Contactez-nous sans obligation.]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Stadthaus mit privatem Grundstück in einem tadellosen Zustand. Reihenhaus in Strandnähe (450 m) sowie ab all jene Dienstleistungen. Große Terrasse hat als auch eine schöne Terrasse und einen Garten. Wohnung mit 3 Schlafzimmer, 2 Bäder, Wohn-Esszimmer mit Kaminofen Cassete, Küche unabhängig, erste Qualitäten (PVC Fenster, Doppelverglasung, Vorhänge...) Möbel und Geräte enthalten. Fragen Sie uns unverbindlich.]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[Casa a schiera con terreno privato in condizioni impeccabili. Villetta a schiera vicino alla spiaggia (450 m), nonché tutti i servizi. Grande terrazza ha così come anche una bella terrazza e giardino. Appartamento con 3 camere da letto, 2 bagni, soggiorno con stufa, cucina indipendente, di prima qualità (finestre di PVC, doppi vetri e persiane...) Mobili ed elettrodomestici inclusi. Contattaci senza impegno.]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>90</h_surface>
    <n_beds>3</n_beds>
    <n_baths>2</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>1</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/2806/greenacres/advert00002.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/2806/greenacres/advert00005.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/2806/greenacres/advert00003.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/2806/greenacres/advert00006.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/2806/greenacres/advert00008.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/2806/greenacres/advert00011.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/2806/greenacres/advert00007.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/2806/greenacres/advert00013.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/2806/greenacres/advert00014.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/2806/greenacres/advert00016.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/2806/greenacres/advert00015.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/2806/greenacres/advert00017.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/2806/greenacres/advert00020.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="14"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/2806/greenacres/advert00021.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="15"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/2806/greenacres/advert00019.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="16"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/2806/greenacres/advert00023.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="17"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/2806/greenacres/advert00024.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>B377</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>105000</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>old</habitat>
    <latitude>38.85941730</latitude>
    <longitude>0.00929097</longitude>
    <mandate_number>B377</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[ADOSADO]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[ADOSADO]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[ADOSADO]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[ADOSADO]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[ADOSADO]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[Townhouse in quiet. Terraced house close to the beach (600m), as well as all the services. Large terrace 2 bedrooms, 1 bathrooms, living room, kitchen. Good qualities. Consult us without commitment]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[Adosado en urbanización tranquila.Adosado cercano a la playa (600m) así como de todos los servicios. Gran terraza  de 2 dormitorios,1 baños,salón , cocina office. Buenas calidades.Consúltenos sin compromiso]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[Maison de ville au calme. Maison mitoyenne à proximité de la plage (600 m), ainsi que tous les services. Grande terrasse 2 chambres, 1 salles de bains, salon, cuisine. Bonnes qualités. Contactez-nous sans engagement]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Reihenhaus in Ruhe. Reihenhaus in der Nähe zum Strand (600 m), sowie alle Dienstleistungen. Große Terrasse, 2 Schlafzimmer, 1 Badezimmer, Wohnzimmer, Küche. Gute Qualitäten. Kontaktieren Sie uns unverbindlich]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[Casa a schiera in zona tranquilla. Villetta a schiera vicino alla spiaggia (600 m), nonché tutti i servizi. Grande terrazza 2 camere da letto, 1 bagni, soggiorno, cucina. Buone qualità. Contattaci senza impegno]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>98</h_surface>
    <n_beds>2</n_beds>
    <n_baths>2</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>0</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1631/greenacres/p7240021.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1631/greenacres/p7240023.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1631/greenacres/p7240024.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1631/greenacres/p7240025.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1631/greenacres/p7240027.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1631/greenacres/p7240026.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>B370</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>128000</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>old</habitat>
    <latitude>38.86310985</latitude>
    <longitude>-0.00148078</longitude>
    <mandate_number>B370</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[TOWNHOUSE IN BOTICARI]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[ADOSADO EN BOTICARI]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[MAISON DE VILLE Boticari]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[STADTHAUS Boticari]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[TOWNHOUSE Boticari]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[Townhouse in quiet. Terraced house close to the beach (600m), as well as all the services. Large terrace and private garden. Apartment de3dormitorios, 2 bathrooms, lounge, kitchen office, first calidades(ventanas y persianas aluminio, doble acristalamiento, puerta blindada,chimenea..) Furniture and appliances included. Consult us without commitment]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[Adosado en urbanización tranquila.Adosado cercano a la playa (600m) así como de todos los servicios. Amplia terraza y jardín privado.Adosado de 3 dormitorios, 2 baños,salón , cocina office, Primeras calidades(ventanas y persianas aluminio, doble acristalamiento, puerta blindada,chimenea..)Muebles y electrodomésticos incluidos.Consúltenos sin compromiso]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[Maison de ville dans une urbanisation tranquille. Maison mitoyenne à proximité de la plage (600 m) aussi bien à partir de tous ces services. Grande terrasse et jardin privé. Appartement de3dormitorios, 2 salles de bains, salon, bureau cuisine, première calidades (ventanas y persianas aluminio, doble acristalamiento, puerta blindada, chimenea..) Meubles et électroménagers inclus. Consultez-nous sans engagement]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Reihenhaus in Ruhe. Reihenhaus in der Nähe zum Strand (600 m), sowie alle Dienstleistungen. Große Terrasse und Garten privat. Wohnung de3dormitorios, 2 Badezimmer, Lounge, Küche Büro, erste Calidades (Ventanas y Persianas Aluminio, Doble Acristalamiento, Puerta Blindada, Chimenea..) Möbel und Geräte enthalten. Kontaktieren Sie uns unverbindlich]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[Casa a schiera in zona tranquilla. Villetta a schiera vicino alla spiaggia (600 m), nonché tutti i servizi. Grande terrazza e giardino privato. De3dormitorios Appartamento, 2 bagni, salone, cucina office, primo calidades (ventanas y persianas aluminio, doble vetri, puerta blindada, chimenea..) Mobili ed elettrodomestici inclusi. Contattaci senza impegno]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>90</h_surface>
    <n_beds>3</n_beds>
    <n_baths>2</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>1</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1629/greenacres/p5220145.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1629/greenacres/p5220146.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1629/greenacres/p5220150.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1629/greenacres/p5220152.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1629/greenacres/p5220154.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1629/greenacres/p5220157.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1629/greenacres/p5220153.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1629/greenacres/p5220159.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1629/greenacres/p5220158.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1629/greenacres/p5220161.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1629/greenacres/p5220160.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1629/greenacres/p5220168.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1629/greenacres/p5220166.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>H459</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>269500</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>luxury</habitat>
    <latitude>38.84668780</latitude>
    <longitude>-0.00466300</longitude>
    <mandate_number>H459</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[COTTAGE]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[CHALET]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[CHALET]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[FERIENHAUS]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[COTTAGE]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[Large independent villa with 667 m2 plot. Three bedrooms, one double, 2 bathrooms (one en suite), living room, swimming-pool, storage room, covered parking,. Contact us without obligation]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[Amplio chalet independiente con parcela de 667 m2. Tres dormitorios, uno de ellos dobles, 2 baños ( Uno de ellos en suite), salón comedor , piscina, trastero, parking cubierto,.Consúltenos sin compromiso]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[Grande villa indépendante avec 667 m2 terrain. Trois chambres à coucher, un lit double, 2 salles de bains (une salle de bains), salon, piscine, salle de stockage, parking, couvert. Contactez-nous sans engagement]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Große freistehende Villa mit 667 m2 Grundstück. Drei Schlafzimmer, eines mit einem Doppelbett, 2 Badezimmer (eins en-suite), Wohnzimmer, Schwimmbad, Lagerung Zimmer, Parkplatz. Kontaktieren Sie uns unverbindlich]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[Grande villa indipendente con 667 m2 trama. Tre camere da letto, una matrimoniale, 2 bagni (uno en suite), sala soggiorno, piscina, ripostiglio, coperto parcheggio. Contattaci senza impegno]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>230</h_surface>
    <n_beds>3</n_beds>
    <n_baths>2</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>1</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3294/greenacres/p1020003.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3294/greenacres/p1020006.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3294/greenacres/p1020010.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3294/greenacres/p1020011.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3294/greenacres/p1020013.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3294/greenacres/p1020015.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3294/greenacres/p1020017.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3294/greenacres/p1020019.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3294/greenacres/p1020018.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3294/greenacres/p1020021.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3294/greenacres/p1020022.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3294/greenacres/p1020023.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3294/greenacres/p1020025.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="14"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3294/greenacres/p1020027.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="15"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3294/greenacres/p1020028.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="16"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3294/greenacres/p1020030.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>H552</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>199500</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>luxury</habitat>
    <latitude>38.85446560</latitude>
    <longitude>0.02004080</longitude>
    <mandate_number>H552</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[CHALET]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[CHALET]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[CHALET]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[CHALET]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[CHALET]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[Detached villa in the town of Els Poblets, 400 m from the beach, close to Denia and Oliva, as well as all the services. Location very quiet, very clear and beautiful views to the plot and the mountain. Excellent state of conservation. The Villa consists of three bedrooms, bathroom, kitchen, pantry, sunroom, corner plot. Fully furnished with appliances included. Contact us without obligation]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[REBAJADO.Chalet  independiente en la población de Els Poblets, a 400 m de la playa, muy cerca de Denia y de Oliva, asi como también de todos los servicios. Emplazamiento muy tranquilo, vistas muy despejadas y bonitas a la parcela y a la montaña. Excelente estado de conservación. El chalet consta de tres dormitorios dobles, baños, cocina independiente, despensa, terraza acristalada, parcela esquinera. Completamente amueblado con electrodomésticos incluidos. Consúltenos sin compromiso]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[Villa individuelle dans la ville d’Els Poblets, à 400 m de la plage, près de Denia et Oliva, ainsi que tous les services. Endroit très calme, très clair et belles vues à l’intrigue et la montagne. Excellent état de conservation. La Villa se compose de trois chambres, salle de bains, cuisine, cellier, véranda, terrain de coin. Entièrement meublée et équipée inclus. Contactez-nous sans engagement]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Freistehende Villa in der Stadt von Els Poblets, 400 m vom Strand entfernt, in der Nähe von Denia und Oliva, sowie alle Dienstleistungen. Lage sehr ruhig, sehr klar und eine herrliche Aussicht auf das Grundstück und die Berge. Ausgezeichneten Zustand der Erhaltung. Die Villa besteht aus drei Schlafzimmern, Bad, Küche, Speisekammer, Wintergarten, Eckgrundstück. Voll möbliert mit Geräte enthalten. Kontaktieren Sie uns unverbindlich]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[Villa indipendente nella città di Els Poblets, 400 m dalla spiaggia, vicino a Denia e Oliva, nonché tutti i servizi. Posizione molto tranquilla, molto chiaro e splendidi panorami la trama e la montagna. Ottimo stato di conservazione. La Villa è composta da tre camere da letto, bagno, cucina, dispensa, veranda, appezzamento di angolo. Completamente arredato con elettrodomestici inclusi. Contattaci senza impegno]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>105</h_surface>
    <n_beds>3</n_beds>
    <n_baths>1</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>0</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3689/greenacres/p3230001.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3689/greenacres/p3230002.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3689/greenacres/p3230004.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3689/greenacres/p3230006.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3689/greenacres/p3230007.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3689/greenacres/p3230009.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3689/greenacres/p3230010.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3689/greenacres/p3230013.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3689/greenacres/p3230015.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3689/greenacres/p3230016.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3689/greenacres/p3230008.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3689/greenacres/p3230018.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3689/greenacres/p3230023.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>H545</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>334000</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>luxury</habitat>
    <latitude>38.85478800</latitude>
    <longitude>0.01727410</longitude>
    <mandate_number>H545</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[CHALET]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[CHALET]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[CHALET]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[CHALET]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[CHALET]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[Gran chalet con dos viviendas independientes. Planta baja, 3 dormitorios, baño, wc, salón comedor, cocina americana. Planta alta: 3 dormitorios, baño, salón comedor, cocina independiente, 2 terrazas cubiertas. Piscina. Parking cubierto. Garage. BBQ. Trasteros.]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[Gran chalet con dos viviendas independientes. Planta baja, 3 dormitorios, baño, wc, salón comedor, cocina americana. Planta alta: 3 dormitorios, baño, salón comedor, cocina independiente, 2 terrazas cubiertas. Piscina. Parking cubierto. Garage. BBQ. Trasteros.]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[Gran chalet con dos viviendas independientes. Planta baja, 3 dormitorios, baño, wc, salón comedor, cocina americana. Planta alta: 3 dormitorios, baño, salón comedor, cocina independiente, 2 terrazas cubiertas. Piscina. Parking cubierto. Garage. BBQ. Trasteros.]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Gran chalet con dos viviendas independientes. Planta baja, 3 dormitorios, baño, wc, salón comedor, cocina americana. Planta alta: 3 dormitorios, baño, salón comedor, cocina independiente, 2 terrazas cubiertas. Piscina. Parking cubierto. Garage. BBQ. Trasteros.]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[Gran chalet con dos viviendas independientes. Planta baja, 3 dormitorios, baño, wc, salón comedor, cocina americana. Planta alta: 3 dormitorios, baño, salón comedor, cocina independiente, 2 terrazas cubiertas. Piscina. Parking cubierto. Garage. BBQ. Trasteros.]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>276</h_surface>
    <n_beds>6</n_beds>
    <n_baths>2</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>0</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250011.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250002.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250004.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250001.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250007.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250006.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250009.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250008.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250012.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250014.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250013.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250015.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250017.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="14"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250019.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="15"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250018.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="16"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250020.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="17"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250021.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="18"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250024.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="19"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250023.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="20"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250025.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="21"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250027.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="22"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250029.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="23"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250030.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="24"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250031.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="25"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250032.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="26"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250033.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="27"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250034.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="28"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250035.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="29"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250036.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="30"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250039.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="31"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250038.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="32"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250041.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="33"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250043.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="34"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250047.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="35"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250046.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="36"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250048.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="37"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250049.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="38"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250052.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="39"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/1660/greenacres/p7250051.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>VmB001</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>109000</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>old</habitat>
    <latitude>38.84898450</latitude>
    <longitude>0.01691040</longitude>
    <mandate_number>VmB001</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[TERRACED HOUSE]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[ADOSADO]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[MAISON MITOYENNE]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[REIHENHAUS]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[CASA A SCHIERA]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[Townhouse 2 bedroom duplex for sale in the center of the municipality of Els Poblets, only 9 km. away from Denia and 2 kms. Beach.
Housing in 2 plants distributed in 2 bedroom (currently one of them converted into a spacious dressing room), a spacious bathroom, a bathroom with shower, living/dining room with access to the common areas, equipped kitchen and 2 large terraces, another front with access to the pool and a rear with access to the street. The House has air conditioning (cold and heat) in bedrooms and living room, electric radiators of low consumption, PVC Windows with double glass, lined wardrobes and satellite connection. Sold unfurnished.
Urbanization with community swimming pool and garden. The property includes garage and storage rooms underground.
Located in the Centre of the town, for easy access to all kinds of services. Sunny and comfortable housing for long periods of time. Contact us without obligation.]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[OFERTA.Adosado dúplex de 2 dormitorios en venta en el centro del municipio de Els Poblets, a tan sólo 9 km. de Denia y 2 kms. de playa.
Vivienda en 2 plantas distribuida en 2 dormitorios (actualmente uno de ellos convertido en un amplio vestidor), un baño amplio, un baño con ducha, salón-comedor con salida a las zonas comunes, cocina independiente equipada y 2 amplias terrazas, una trasera con acceso a la calle y otra delantera con salida a la piscina. El adosado dispone de aparatos de aire acondicionado (frío y calor) en dormitorios y salón comedor, radiadores eléctricos de bajo consumo, ventanas de PVC con doble cristal, armarios empotrados forrados y conexión satélite. Se vende sin muebles.
Urbanización con jardín y piscina comunitarios. La vivienda incluye plaza de garaje y trasteros subterráneos.
Ubicado en el centro de la población, para fácil acceso a todo tipo de servicios. Una vivienda cómoda y soleada para disfrutar de largas temporadas. Consúltenos sin compromiso.]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[Duplex à vendre dans le centre de la municipalité de Els Poblets, à seulement 9 km de Denia et à 2 kms de chambres maison de ville 2. Plage.
Logement dans 2 usines réparties dans 2 chambres à coucher (actuellement une transformée en un spacieux dressing), une salle de bains, une salle de bains avec douche, salon/salle à manger avec accès aux espaces communs, cuisine équipée et 2 grandes terrasses, un autre front avec accès à la piscine et une arrière avec accès à la rue. La maison dispose de la climatisation (froid et chaleur) dans les chambres et salle de séjour, radiateurs électriques de faible consommation, fenêtres en PVC avec double vitrage, placards, bordé connexion satellite. Vendu non meublé.
Urbanisation avec piscine communautaire et jardin. La propriété comprend des chambres garage et de stockage souterrains.
Situé dans le Centre de la ville, pour un accès facile à toutes sortes de services. Logement ensoleillé et confortable pendant de longues périodes de temps. Contactez-nous sans obligation.]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Townhouse 2 Schlafzimmer duplex zu verkaufen in der Mitte der Gemeinde Els Poblets, nur 9 km von Denia und 2 km entfernt. Strand.
Gehäuse in 2 Werken in 2 Schlafzimmer (derzeit einer von ihnen in ein geräumiges Ankleidezimmer umgewandelt), ein geräumiges Bad, ein Bad mit Dusche, Wohn-/Esszimmer mit Zugang zu den öffentlichen Bereichen verteilt, ausgestattete Küche und 2 große Terrassen, eine andere Front mit Zugang zum Pool und eine hintere mit Zugang zur Straße. Das Haus verfügt über Klimaanlage (Kälte und Wärme) in den Schlafzimmern und Wohnzimmer, elektrische Heizkörper des niedrigen Verbrauchs, PVC-Fenster mit Doppelverglasung, gefüttert, Schränke und Sat-Anschluss. Unmöbliert verkauft.
Wohnanlage mit Gemeinschaftspool und Garten. Das Anwesen verfügt über Garage und Abstellraum Zimmer u.
Das Hotel liegt im Zentrum der Stadt, für einfachen Zugriff auf alle Arten von Dienstleistungen. Sonnige und komfortable Wohnung für längere Zeit. Kontaktieren Sie uns unverbindlich.]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[Camera da letto casa a schiera 2 duplex in vendita nel centro del comune di Els Poblets, solo 9 km lontano da Denia e a 2 km. Spiaggia.
Alloggio in 2 stabilimenti distribuiti in 2 camere da letto (attualmente uno di loro trasformato in un ampio spogliatoio), un ampio bagno, un bagno con doccia, soggiorno/sala da pranzo con accesso alle aree comuni, cucina attrezzata e 2 ampie terrazze, un altro fronte con accesso alla piscina e una posteriore con accesso alla strada. La casa dispone di aria condizionata (freddo e caldo) nelle camere da letto e salotto, radiatori elettrici a basso consumo, finestre in PVC con doppio vetro, foderato armadi e collegamento satellitare. Venduto ammobiliato.
Urbanizzazione con piscina ad uso condominiale e giardino. La proprietà comprende garage e deposito sale sotterranee.
Situato nel centro della città, per un facile accesso a tutti i tipi di servizi. Soleggiato e confortevole alloggio per lunghi periodi di tempo. Contattaci senza impegno.]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>78</h_surface>
    <n_beds>2</n_beds>
    <n_baths>2</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>0</precise_location>
    <furnished>0</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3637/greenacres/4.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3637/greenacres/16.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3637/greenacres/2.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3637/greenacres/3.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3637/greenacres/5.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="6"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3637/greenacres/58e36913b0513_1.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="7"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3637/greenacres/7.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="8"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3637/greenacres/8.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="9"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3637/greenacres/6.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="10"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3637/greenacres/10.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="11"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3637/greenacres/15.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="12"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3637/greenacres/11.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="13"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3637/greenacres/12.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="14"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3637/greenacres/9.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="15"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3637/greenacres/13.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="16"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/3637/greenacres/14.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
   <advert>
    <account_id>49799a</account_id>
    <reference>VmL001</reference>
    <type>properties</type>
    <price>150000</price>
    <has_included_fees>0</has_included_fees>
    <agency_rates_type>2</agency_rates_type>
    <currency>EUR</currency>
    <commune>Alicante/Alacant</commune>
    <country_code>ES</country_code>
    <habitat>business</habitat>
    <latitude>38.83634960</latitude>
    <longitude>0.10747120</longitude>
    <mandate_number>VmL001</mandate_number>
    <title_en><![CDATA[Local]]></title_en>
    <title_es><![CDATA[Local]]></title_es>
    <title_fr><![CDATA[Local]]></title_fr>
    <title_de><![CDATA[Lokale]]></title_de>
    <title_it><![CDATA[Locale]]></title_it>
    <summary_en><![CDATA[Local shopping downtown, in very State, of 100 m² in plant low over 35 m² of loft / warehouse. It has air conditioning, adapted bath, large showcase, 7 meters of façade and 5 meters of height.]]></summary_en>
    <summary_es><![CDATA[Local comercial céntrico, en  muy estado, de 100 m² en planta baja más 35 m² de altillo/almacén. Dispone de aire acondicionado, baño adaptado, amplio escaparate, 7 metros de fachada y 5 metros de altura libre.]]></summary_es>
    <summary_fr><![CDATA[Des magasins du centre-ville, dans le même État, de 100 m² dans la plante basse sur 35 m² de loft / entrepôt. Caractéristiques de l’air conditionné, salle de bain adaptée, vitrine large, 7 mètres de façade et 5 mètres de hauteur libre.]]></summary_fr>
    <summary_de><![CDATA[Geschäfte in der Innenstadt, in sehr Zustand, 100 m ² große Anlage niedrig über 35 m ² Loft / Lager. Funktionen der Klimaanlage, Badezimmer angepasst, große Schaufenster, 7 Meter Fassade und 5 Metern Höhe frei.]]></summary_de>
    <summary_it><![CDATA[Shopping in centro, locale molto stato, di 100 m ² in pianta bassa oltre 35 m ² di loft / magazzino. Dispone di aria condizionata, bagno adattato, ampia vetrina, 7 metri di facciata e 5 metri di altezza libera.]]></summary_it>
    <h_surface>135</h_surface>
    <n_beds>2</n_beds>
    <n_baths>1</n_baths>
    <dpe_type></dpe_type>
    <precise_location>1</precise_location>
    <furnished>0</furnished>
    <pics>
     <pic order="1"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/2448/greenacres/584e70ffd329e_1.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="2"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/2448/greenacres/584e70ffd5094_2.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="3"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/2448/greenacres/584e70ffd5b5e_3.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="4"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/2448/greenacres/584e70ffd6c50_4.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
     <pic order="5"><![CDATA[http://www.inmovicmar.com/sites/73/properties/2448/greenacres/584e70ffd7817_5.jpg.jpg]]></pic>
    </pics>
   </advert>
  </add_adverts>
 </Body>
</Envelope>
